(This program may contain indirect advertisements.)
(Running Man)
There are three grand dukes...
who rule over the peaceful Running Empire.
(They all had a clear sense of what they wanted.)
Each of them governs their domain in their own way.
- The first grand duke. - This is really good.
(The first Grand Duke, boasting the empire's finest feast)
This is nice.
(What?)
(Chomping)
The Grand Duke of the Belly indulges in food binges at all hours.
He believes that belly fat is power.
There's a belly that sticks out just right.
(Bulging)
- Yours look quite tolerable. - Right.
(A title seized through voracious appetite alone)
- This is so good. - Right.
I went to the hospital after getting hit by a golf ball,
and I heard I survived thanks to my belly fat.
(Generous belly fat that even spared his life)
It felt as if my flesh was being ripped away.
Nothing is impossible when it comes to my appetite!
(Yang Se Chan, the Grand Duke of the Belly)
- The second grand duke is... - "The grand duke..."
(Surrounded by documents...)
- busy attending to state affairs... - "Fee..."
(and tending to affairs of state, was the second Grand Duke.)
- as always today. - "Official..."
Month.
It's September 13.
(September 13, Haha)
Darn it.
(He has a spotless, crystal-clear soul.)
He is the owner of a spotless, crystal-clear soul.
A monarch is...
Darn it.
I can't even memorize this.
A monarch is...
someone who shows it through actions, not brains.
(Haha, the Grand Duke of the Fools)
Empty Head!
(Ruling over the freezing northern lands)
The last grand duke living in the northern territory.
(The third Grand Duke, radiating an iron-blooded aura)
(The epitome of the Grand Duke of the North will be revealed soon.)
This is a wedding hall.
(The three Grand Dukes will gather in this banquet hall.)
Hello.
Okay! Have a nice day.
- Gosh. - That's a greeting for...
(You can tell he is a townsperson.)
- when you're wrapping things up. - Is that so?
- Good morning. - Hello.
(The Grand Dukes enter draped in faux mink.)
What's wrong with them? This is so embarrassing.
- Good morning. Oh, dear. - Gosh, seriously...
- What's this? - What's wrong with them?
(Tapping)
Why are you dressed like that?
(Patting)
- What's with you? - What are you doing?
Today, we're the stars of the show.
(Totally absorbed in playing the main character)
- Yes, but... - What is this for?
We saw today's guests.
I get it. You're Wolverine, right?
I get it. You're Hwang Jae Gyun, the designer.
(They look alike.)
Wolverine.
- Hwang Jae Gyun, the designer. - Wolverine.
(A glitch in the romance-fantasy world)
- Aren't you Hwang Jae Gyun? - He's Wolverine.
- I'm Tae Jin Ah. - By the way,
(Confused)
what's going on today? We dressed plainly.
- We look modest. - We're keeping it low-key.
(Modest?)
- No, that's somewhat flashy. - You don't look modest.
(A leopard hiding in between the townspeople)
- But I... - What's with you?
- She's a cavewoman. - I added a little flair.
You added a little flair?
- Why do you sound so bashful? - You sound shy.
- So, this is... - Leopard.
(A modestly flirty leopard-print look)
I just added a tiny touch of flair.
You look good.
Ye Eun, you look nice. You look like a college student.
I just kept it simple.
You look pretty today.
(Simple)
- You think so? - Yes.
- She will get changed soon. - You look like a college girl.
(The bride-to-be kept it simple to save the glam for December.)
- I'm a college girl today. - Right.
We have guests joining us today.
(The special guests for today!)
- The real deal is coming. - What? Wait.
What a triumphant return.
(The real Grand Duke is here to put the fake ones on edge.)
SAN is coming.
- This is it. - He's here.
- The real deal is coming. - What? Wait.
- What a triumphant return. - SAN is coming.
(Everyone is doing it! Currently the hottest thing!)
- This is it. - He's here.
SAN is coming.
(SAN of ATEEZ)
(The global idols ATEEZ,)
(who have claimed the top of the Billboard 200 3 times over)
(The first K-pop boy band at Coachella,)
(ATEEZ has written a new history.)
(Sweeping fans off their feet with powerful performances!)
(He targets the global fans with heart-bouncing moves of "Bad.")
(SAN's "Let's all die" part shook the whole world.)
There's SAN of ATEEZ.
(Just when the Running Empire is bringing the challenge to an end,)
- SAN, I did it. - SAN.
(he finally steps up to defend the dignity of the original.)
If it is what you desire, I'll hand over the empire to you.
(SAN, the Grand Duke of the North)
Good. We'll just go with the other one.
(Chuckling)
- Straighten your back. - Okay.
(Staff)
(The Grand Duke of the North is cringing at the over-the-top theme.)
I suddenly feel like my shoulders are shrinking.
I feel like my shoulders have shrunk to nothing.
(Shy)
- Hey. Come over here. - Hello.
(Behind the Grand Duke of the North from a romance fantasy...)
- It's been a while. - Look at you, Ji Eun.
(Actress, Han Ji Eun)
You look so pretty with your hair cut short.
(A chameleonic all-rounder...)
(who seamlessly melts into every role across any genre!)
I'm here on patrol.
To catch a punk like you.
- They were college classmates. - We went to the same school.
(So Min's friend from college, Ji Eun)
- Tell us a lot about So Min. - Tell us about So Min.
- It wasn't quite clean. - Are you talking about me?
(The history of the Dream Team Girls with so much to expose)
- I mean... - "Me?"
(Sinusitis acting)
Honey, how is this?
(The pretty, clear-eyed mad girl is back after 3 years.)
What is this?
Hey.
(Today, she is here as the Grand Duchess.)
- Hello. - Hey.
- SAN! - What...
(Flapping)
(The Grand Duke of the North receives an enthusiastic welcome.)
- All right. - He's here.
My goodness. You're back after becoming a big star.
Oh, dear.
(The grand dukes bump their chests right away.)
It's been a while, Ji Eun.
- My goodness. Hey, why you... - Your hair looks great.
It's been a while.
You look so pretty with your hair cut short.
(Ji Eun came back with a fresh haircut.)
Why did you come back looking so pretty?
Hey, you look great with a haircut.
- What? - A haircut. It's hair styling.
(To a lady)
- You look great with your new hair. - Thank you.
(The Grand Duke of the Fools lives up to his name.)
- I love your tiara. - Not many people...
(Totally rocking the short haircut)
can pull off a short haircut like that.
Are you in love now? You've become a lot prettier.
You look gorgeous.
- I recently got a haircut. - You did?
Did something happen?
No. A project of mine...
just wrapped up,
so I had a little break. I thought it was my chance.
(This is her first bold look in her 20-year career!)
- You look younger. - It looks amazing.
- So, SAN is here today. - It's a triumphant return.
(SAN made a triumphant return after five years.)
Five years ago, he was running all over the place,
struggling to pop balloons.
- He was like this. - He was fighting a battle alone.
(SAN filmed a solo spy movie with balloons strapped to his back.)
- In his mouth... - Why is he biting on that thing?
What's that?
You think you're looking so cool now, right?
I think so.
(The 22-year-old SAN had a severe case of main character syndrome.)
- He was like that. - He's not the same SAN anymore.
(Flushed)
- SAN was running around the hills. - Right.
- Exactly. - And soap bubbles.
- He's not the same SAN from before. - He didn't pop the balloons well.
- No. - I tried, though.
- Yes, he did. - He did try hard.
- He worked hard. - We know.
(Now he's back, shaking up the entire world as a real star.)
- He was full of passion. - That's true.
He's not the same SAN from before.
He looks so cool and charming.
What kind of life are you living these days, SAN?
- Doesn't it feel unreal? - These days,
I feel like I'm getting so much love.
(Thankfully)
You're receiving love all over the world.
- Right. - ATEEZ has always been popular.
(ATEEZ wins hearts around the world once again with "Bad.")
- They're very popular. - ATEEZ has always been popular.
But SAN has become even more popular than that.
When I saw their new performance of "Bad,"
I was shocked by the last part where SAN appeared.
(Pursed)
- SAN is really... - That's it. While doing that,
you shouldn't make that expression with your mouth. With a glare...
Who's teaching whom here?
- Wait. - Don't do that with your mouth.
(He gives some tips as a senior artist.)
- Just stay quiet. - The thing from your music video.
- You were like this with a gaze. - Just stay quiet.
- Mr. Jo Young Nam, just stay still. - Jo Young Nam?
- Show us how you do it. - Let's see.
- "Bad." - I want to see the original.
- I want to see it in person. - "Bad.
(There were tons of chest-popping contenders.)
This is my first time seeing it in person.
Okay, SAN!
Let's go, SAN!
(The original Grand Duke's "Bad" on a whole different level)
I finally get to see it.
(Looking forward)
- There you go! - All right.
All right. This is it.
That's the expression. That's what I'm talking about.
(Excited)
- That's the face. - Oh, dear.
(Fatal charm)
- Yes, this is it. - That's the face.
- He doesn't smile a lot. - That's the face.
(The unruly, unwanted dance move sneaks its way in.)
- There you go. - This is it.
My goodness.
He looks so composed and at ease.
That was amazing.
(His retrained elegance is about to pull everyone into the fandom.)
That's so cool.
- That's so cool. - Se Chan.
(He looks so cool!)
- Se Chan, we should do it. - It's not too much.
(Overwhelmed to see it live)
He looks so composed.
The three of us should dance together.
(Between the Grand Dukes)
- All right. - Dance again with us on your sides.
- Let's do that. - Let's dance together.
- With you? - Let's put one together.
(The Blowfly Grand Dukes gather at the chance to get views.)
- Okay. - Let's make a clip out of this.
- Great. - The Grand Duke of the North...
- Those darn flies. - Those blowflies.
(All fired up for the collaboration of a lifetime)
Those blowflies.
It just keeps getting worse.
(Belly flopping)
- This is the worst. - I'm good at this.
This is so disgusting.
You're blocking SAN!
(Displeased)
- This is so pathetic. - Let's do this at the end.
(Amid all that)
Okay. A heart at the end.
It's so embarrassing.
All right.
- Ji Eun... - You are ruining it.
(Only SAN shines in this heart ending.)
That was so cool.
(Immersed)
- We did it! - We made it!
(The "Bad" club, where only the blowflies are satisfied, is made.)
- Ji Eun. - Yes?
- Can you do this? - That was so cool.
(Of course.)
- She can do it. - That's it.
- Hey, move over. - Move.
(Shoo)
- We did it! - Move. Ji Eun is dancing.
- Ji Eun is doing it. - Move over.
(She goes to the center after swatting away the blowflies.)
Come here, Ji Eun.
- Am I dancing alone? - Yes, do it alone.
- I'll stand behind you. - Dance together.
- I'll stay here. - But...
- All right. - How do I do this?
(Sudden change)
(Surprised)
- She's quite good. - That's good.
- You're doing very well. - It's quite nice.
You're good.
(Disciplined)
That was pretty good.
- You're good. - It's not bad.
(The Grand Duchess reveals her hidden dance instincts.)
You dance well.
(Dancing gently)
Make a heart.
(Vibing)
Finish it with a heart.
What was this?
(The ultimate high-society ball that will shake the empire)
- You're good. - You sure can dance.
That was really good.
- Thank you. - You've done this before.
(Clapping)
Gosh, SAN!
(The class of the original Grand Duke of the North)
- Great. - He looks so cool and charming.
- So this is what's charming. - Exactly.
So, have you been making...
some money? How are things going?
Well, very much.
(Young and rich)
Congratulations!
- You're making some money? - You should save up your money now.
(Butting in)
SAN.
While filming the music video,
(Did you sense something during the music video shoot?)
did you expect it to blow up like this?
- Did you see this coming? - Did you expect it?
- I figured fans would love it, - The fans.
but I had no idea...
the general public would love it this much.
(The part that shook the world with every chest pop)
- SAN's makeup, facial expressions, - Exactly.
(The perfect combination of visuals, expressions, and dance)
- and dance moves were just perfect. - That's true.
Plus,
- SAN's physique. - His physique.
(Massive 52cm-wide shoulders)
- That's right. - His broad shoulders.
- I knew... - Jong Kook keeps...
bragging that SAN goes to his gym.
- Right. - No, that's not it.
SAN has always been passionate...
(He had been asking Trainer Kook for advice.)
- Right. - about working out.
Jong Kook once told me this.
"SAN, your shoulders and back look amazing,"
(Jong Kook said...)
"but if you work on your chest a little more, you'll look perfect."
- Your back muscles are incredible. - Yes. I worked out hard.
(A genetically flawless frame)
You need to put a bit more focus on chest development.
(Trainer Kook gave him a chest workout prescription.)
Okay.
Focus heavily on muscle isolation in the beginning.
- I said he'd look perfect. - Ever since,
I've been going all-in on chest workouts.
So Jong Kook practically raised you.
Anyway, I told SAN,
"You have the kind of face that demands a great physique."
(Seeing ahead)
(Jong Kook built him with muscles.)
His face and body just match up so well now.
And SAN is called the Grand Duke of the North.
- The Grand Duke of the North. - Right.
Do you know what the Grand Duke of the North is?
- I don't know. - Then why...
(Chuckling)
- I'm just pretending to know. - You're really...
(He just pretended to know.)
I just pretend to know.
- Is it a kind of duke in the UK? - So, it's from...
(A cold, handsome ruler...)
- web novels. - Exactly.
(of the rugged northern land,)
It means men with this cold, striking charm from the North.
(who is dangerously charming)
(He is the live version, straight out of the romance fantasy.)
- The Grand Duke of the North. - So...
- Is that it? - he's the Grand Duke of the North.
And he's the Grand Duke of the Belly.
(This is just the Grand Duke of the Belly.)
- He's the Grand Duke of the Belly. - The Grand Duke of the Belly.
Are you imitating SAN?
(Speechless)
- Yes. - He's dressed like SAN.
- SAN is... - SAN, going from bad to worse.
He's SAN, going from bad to worse.
(Belly going from bad to worse, SAN)
Why are you imitating SAN?
So I was sitting at the salon getting my makeup done,
looking like this.
And actual idols were sitting right next to me.
My makeup was way more intense than theirs.
It was so embarrassing.
(He went harder on the prep than active idols.)
- So, you're SAN. - And we have Hwang Jae Gyun.
- No! - Hwang Jae Gyun, the designer.
I'm Busan.
- What? - He's Busan.
He's SAN, going from bad to worse, and he's a Busan wannabe.
(Busan, going from bad to worse)
I see. That's what he claims.
- You're not from Busan, are you? - No, he's not.
- He says that to make money. - I was born in Stuttgart.
(Birthplace)
- It's not about money. - What?
He went with Jamaica at first, but it wasn't so lucrative.
- So he switched to Busan. - Busan.
But you don't use a dialect.
That's not true!
He's doing that for money.
- That's not a real Busan dialect. - Yes, it is.
- Where are you from? - Can you tell that?
I'm from Namhae, Gyeongsangnam-do.
You should've told me sooner.
(His Busan side jumps out, trying to find any connection.)
- It's so good to see you. - Stop it.
- We need to talk. - But...
That's not a real dialect. It's fake.
It's not fake!
(The fake dialect no one can tolerate)
That doesn't sound right.
That's not true. This is the Busan dialect.
(The fake persona is taken over by the concept.)
Everyone is having a hard time because of that.
They wonder where he is from.
Ji Eun, I hear that you're learning Italian.
- Italian? - Are you learning Italian?
Italian?
Yes. I'm going to Italy soon.
- You're going there? - Yes.
- Show us what you've learned. - How do you speak Italian?
(Curious about her skills)
I only know how to say hello.
- Show us. - Let us hear it.
Buongiorno.
(Holding back laughter)
- Ji Eun. - Hey.
I thought you were doing an impression of Bobby Kim.
"Buongiorno."
Ji Eun.
We can do that much too.
What else can you speak?
- Ciao. - Ciao.
Bye. Ciao.
- Buonasera. - What?
- Buonasera. - What is she saying?
- "Buonasera?" - What?
These are an evening greeting and a daytime greeting.
(She learned the greeting first.)
Can you even really call this studying?
Didn't you just look through an Italian guidebook?
- Ji Eun isn't an average person. - No.
You all know that.
(Looking forward to the chaos from the maniac Grand Duchess)
- Sure. - You'll see it after some time.
Today, with SAN, the Grand Duke of the North,
and Imperial Princess Han Ji Eun,
who look like characters straight out of a romance fantasy novel,
we are having the grand duke, There Is an Outsider Among Us Race.
- What is that? - SAN, the Grand Duke of the North,
Yang Se Chan, the Grand Duke of the Belly,
and Haha, the Grand Duke of the Fools are the captains.
(The three Grand Dukes will be the team leaders.)
- I see. - Why?
Two outsiders have snuck...
into the territory ruled by the grand dukes.
Who are the outsiders?
After the race is over,
the grand dukes and the townspeople...
will point out two suspicious people...
and send them off to exile.
- To exile? - Yes.
If they succeed in the arrest,
it's a victory for the grand dukes and the townspeople,
and they get a prize.
If they fail, it's a victory for the outsiders,
and the grand dukes and the townspeople get a penalty.
But the three grand dukes...
aren't outsiders.
- They aren't outsiders. - Not them?
(The 2 outsiders are...)
- Those three aren't the spies. - Is that so?
They are not the spies.
(hidden within these 6 people!)
- One, two, three... - There are too many of us.
That narrows the odds down significantly.
- There aren't that many left. - Right. It narrows it down a lot.
- It's 2 out of 6. - Right.
(Staring)
I was a spy just a little while ago.
- You could do that again. - Come on.
- Maybe it's Ji Eun. - All right.
(Suspicions are already growing.)
I'll divide you into teams.
Team North will be...
SAN, Yu Jae Seok, and Ji Ye Eun.
- Ye Eun. - Team Belly will be...
Yang Se Chan, Kim Jong Kook, and Song Ji Hyo.
Okay!
Team Fools will be Haha, Jee Seok Jin,
- and Han Ji Eun. - Okay!
- Ji Eun is... - All right.
(High five)
- Welcome. - Welcome to the team.
- Ji Eun, your palms are sweating. - We have to spot the spies.
My hands and feet are always cold.
(Don't suspect me.)
- So, there are two outsiders? - What did he say?
(There are 2 outsiders?)
My team could have two outsiders.
Sure.
Before the mission begins,
we'll give each grand duke gift certificates worth 100 dollars.
- Really? - Yes.
Are they real?
All right.
- They are real. - Yes.
The gift certificates will also be used as prizes for the winning team,
(It will be the prize if they succeed in catching the outsiders.)
- so please keep them safe. - Okay.
And the team that loses today's missions...
- will be disbanded. - What?
They will be absorbed into the opposing team.
The certificates that the grand duke of the losing team was holding...
will also be transferred...
- to the absorbing team. - Really?
- Let's do this. - This is hard.
- It's hard to single out the spies. - It's so hard.
(They need to protect the team by winning the missions,)
- It's really tricky. - It is.
(while finding the hidden outsiders!)
We'll proceed with the mission right here.
- Right here? - What's the mission?
- What is this? - What is it?
(The foot mats are set up for the first mission.)
Okay.
Captain Wolverine, sit here.
Wolverine.
(Glancing)
Captain Wolverine is here.
Ye Eun keeps glancing over at me.
Se Chan, it's really...
- She's secretly peeking at me. - Button up your shirt.
(Bare skin peeking through the flowing fabric)
- She did keep glancing over. - I know.
I can't help it.
- Look at her eyes. - She keeps looking.
She keeps glancing over secretly.
I just can't help it.
But is this okay for viewers under the age of 15?
- They say I'm fine. - As long as nipples don't show?
- Right. - Okay.
(The most harmless softie in the world)
They say my nipples are okay.
- Really? - Yours stick out too much.
There must be a body...
that's okay to show off. Right?
All right. This mission is called...
(Mission 1, Empty Hands Make a Loud Racket)
Empty Hands Make a Loud Racket.
What is it?
One member from each team comes forward...
and passes two sponge sticks...
in one direction to the rhythm of the song.
When the song stops while passing the sticks,
the members holding the sticks...
must immediately hit the head of the member with empty hands.
If you hit the wrong member holding the sticks,
hesitate and hit too late, or fail to hit them at all,
- it's minus one point. - We have to hit them right away.
(Minus 1 point)
We'll tally up the final scores,
and the team with the highest score wins.
You will play with a clue about the outsiders on the line.
Okay.
The first matchup will be between the grand dukes.
- The grand dukes. - Let's go, grand dukes.
The Grand Duke of the Belly.
- What is he? - He's the Grand Duke of the Belly.
(His strength comes from his belly, the Grand Duke of the Belly)
The Grand Duke of the Belly.
Designer Hwang Jae Gyun.
(The Godfather of the Empty Heads, Grand Duke of the Fools)
(Successfully bulked up, the Grand Duke of the North)
It will be fun.
The only true grand duke is SAN,
and the rest of them are all fake.
- We are also grand dukes. - Wolverine.
We are dukes anyway.
(Taking it off)
He's giving us a heart attack.
(Intimidating everyone with his belly)
(Eye-catching)
- How does this go? - Wait.
- Grand Duke of the Belly. - Yes?
- Button up your shirt. - Right.
I can't back down, but I'll button up just one.
That's too...
It's just that your breasts keep sticking out.
(Annoyed)
- Okay. Good. - All right.
(It was a good attention-catcher.)
I see something from here.
Say hello to them, you brat.
- Hello. - They're shy.
They keep sneaking glances at me.
Like this.
- His belly looks like a baby's. - A baby?
Okay.
(They will warm up with a practice game.)
- Let's play a practice round. - All right.
(The baton will be passed on clockwise.)
Let's go, Haha!
Throwing stones, pong-dang pong-dang
- Throwing stones secretly... - Let's go!
(The music stops.)
(SAN's hands are empty.)
It goes like that?
Why are you hitting me? You should be hitting him.
- Oh, right. You have it. - That's how it works?
(When the music stops, hit the one with empty hands.)
We should hit the one without a stick.
- The music stops like that? - The one without a stick.
(Understood.)
So we don't know when the music will stop.
(They don't know when the music will stop, so they should be quick.)
It stops randomly.
Oh, no. That's scary.
I have a feeling that I'm going to get hit hard.
Ready.
(Round 1 of the grand duke match begins.)
Together.
One, two.
Throwing stones, pong-dang pong-dang
- Throwing stones... - Throwing stones...
(The music stops.)
(What?)
- Throwing stones... - Throwing stones...
(He tosses it to Haha.)
(SAN is empty-handed.)
(Those with sticks hit each other once.)
(Thank you.)
You should hit him.
What are you guys doing?
- Can't you hit him? - You should hit SAN.
- They can't hit him. - Hey.
(They are hesitating in front of the global star.)
How would we hit him?
Are you not hitting him because he's a global star?
You said it had to be quick, so...
(Explaining)
Jong Kook, I hit Haha because I was startled.
(Explaining again)
- I hit him because he hit me. - Because you were upset?
(The Global Grand Duke's safety matters more than the score.)
That can happen.
- Why did you hit me? - Sorry.
I don't think they can ever hit SAN.
- They just can't. - They can't hit him.
We should hit him at the same time.
(Fool -1, North 0, Belly -1)
You should hit the person without a stick.
You hit the one without a stick.
- The one without a stick. - The one without a stick.
- Don't try to be funny. - Do it right.
- You started it. - This is way too forced.
But you started it first.
- You... - Hang on.
- Are you losing on purpose? - Why would I do that?
- The grand dukes... - I'm not a spy.
(There are no outsiders among the Grand Dukes.)
- He can't be an outsider. - The grand dukes aren't outsiders.
- We're not outsiders. - We're just trying hard.
You mean the spies?
(Suspicious)
Isn't Jong Kook an outsider?
- That could be the case. - He's being suspicious.
We have to win to find out the outsiders.
(Is Jong Kook the outsider after all that confident guessing?)
Then play properly.
Play the music.
(The music plays.)
(The music stops.)
(SAN is empty-handed again.)
(Smack)
Hey! Darn it!
(The grand dukes chose the easy way out.)
- SAN... - Why can't you hit him?
- Why... - What's wrong?
- What... - Why hit him instead?
It's not that. He...
(He tries to explain himself, but...)
- We need the points. - Listen.
- Listen. No, it's... - Why fight among yourselves?
(Speechless)
- Why fight among yourselves? - No, it's...
- Se Chan... - Let them hit you.
SAN. You must be incredibly popular.
- Do you feel threatened? - No.
Because he's popular?
- Not at all. - They're intimidated.
They fear for their futures.
SAN, do you want them to hit you?
How do you want the game to go?
- They can comfortably... - We should play the game.
- Comfortably... - We don't mind.
(Desperate)
- Good. - We just play.
SAN had a strict upbringing.
(Fool -2, North 0, Belly -2)
- Relax and play. - They're intimidated by his fame.
(The music plays.)
(The music stops.)
(Now they're playing in earnest.)
Nice one.
Hey. You're quick.
- No, that's the right timing. - He's quick.
(Satisfied)
Okay. Well played.
(Fool -2, North 0, Belly -2)
- Thank you. - Let's play on.
(The music plays.)
Okay.
(Gets revenge)
Yes.
(A full swing)
- Okay. - What?
- What's wrong? - Come on. Let's play!
(Grand Duke of the Belly loses it at the full swing.)
- They hit too hard. - SAN. You're doing well.
Keep aggravating me.
(Thrilling)
- I will. - You must hit hard.
(The music plays.)
(Super focused)
(The music stops.)
(Oh, whatever!)
Darn you.
(A slugfest breaks out.)
- Hey! - Stop.
- Come on. - Why...
(Flustered)
- Move. - This won't do.
- Quit playing. - That's enough.
You really...
(Tossing)
No, guys. What are you doing?
(The grand dukes have zero decorum.)
- Come on. Fight. - They're sworn enemies.
(They make up with a quick dance.)
- Get back here. - That was so funny.
(Fool -3, North 0, Belly -3)
(Shattered dignity)
- Gosh. - This isn't good.
- Okay. - That was insane.
(The players for Round 2 enter.)
- Come on in. - Okay.
(Seok Jin versus Jong Kook versus Jae Seok)
Oh, gosh. This looks bad for me.
- You weakling. - Okay.
(The oldest of each team comes up.)
This isn't good.
It's a simple song.
- Do we have to match the beat? - Pong-dang pong-dang.
(The song)
- Pong... - We can go faster.
- Follow the beat? - Go faster.
(He makes up a rule as soon as he steps up.)
- What? - Just keep moving.
- Okay. - Ignore the beat.
(Rule: Pass it around regardless of the beat.)
- Let's be quick. - Got it.
Yes, just pass it on.
A pause ruins everything.
Yes, just keep passing it.
We'll play the song.
(The music plays.)
- Okay. - Okay.
(Jong Kook and Jae Seok each have one.)
(Twirling)
They're quick.
Darn you.
(A slugfest)
Hey, it hurts. Okay!
- Hey, it hurts. Okay! - What is it?
(They have a clear target.)
- You hit just once! - Just one hit.
- Just one hit. - Just one?
- I didn't know. - Sorry. My bad.
(Brazen)
- We should hit just once. - How many times was that?
- How many hits did you count? - I didn't know.
You tried to get away, so...
- Don't try to run away. - We'll hit just once.
- Don't try to run. - Just once?
- No, let's do this. - What?
(Fuming)
Let's hit many times.
- Are you sure? - Let's stick to one hit.
- Let's stick with one hit. - I suffered multiple hits.
- One is fine. - Even so...
- You hit me loads. - Let's just hit once.
(They had fun hitting him, but now they don’t want to get hit.)
- We didn't know. - We forgot.
- Let's play once more. - We all make mistakes.
No. Let's play one more round with multiple hits.
- Fine. - Okay.
- I want revenge. - Okay.
(They reluctantly agree on a slugfest, vowing revenge.)
We go the same way?
(The music plays.)
(Nostrils flaring)
(Focused pouting)
(The batons go around like propeller blades.)
(Seok Sam got it.)
(Will he get his revenge?)
(Smack)
(He gets beaten up.)
Hit him just once!
This is what he wanted!
(Why, you...)
You wanted to play one more round with multiple hits.
(Seok Sam got hit 13 times in 2 rounds.)
- What are you doing? - He snatched it.
Why did you steal his baton?
Why didn't you give it back?
- This is way more fun. - How could you?
- Sorry. It was instinctual. - This is more fun.
(This is not how it's supposed to be, but they are having fun.)
It's more fun to ignore the rhythm.
- Going faster is better. - It was instinctual.
- Just one hit now? - Just one hit.
- Just one hit. - Pong-dang.
(They correct it to one hit.)
You need to steal the baton.
(The game resumes.)
I'm nervous.
(He got it at last!)
(Smack)
(You fools!)
- What is this? - What is this?
Mister!
You messed up.
- Why did you hit him? - I don't know.
- Don't hit me. - I didn't think.
(He lost a point and succeeded in getting revenge.)
- You lose a point. - You were right.
- I didn't think. - Don't hit me.
(Fool -4, North 0, Belly -3)
Move to the beat of the song!
- Ready? - This is why you need a rhythm.
(Now they will play to the beat.)
Like this?
(Bam!)
(Teeth clenched)
- Oh, no. - Hey.
- Sorry. - Why hit me?
(I have a baton.)
You didn't have...
It wasn't me!
(He thought Seok Sam wouldn't get it for sure.)
This happens.
- It's confusing. - This happens.
(Fool -4, North 0, Belly -4)
- Sorry. - Sorry.
- This game... - Do you want to hit me?
(Emotional)
- You hit before you think. - Okay.
Switch places, Seok Jin.
Take Jong Kook's spot.
- Why? Is it better? - It is.
- Let's swap spots. - No, thanks.
(The childish ego battle begins.)
- Let him swap. - I don't want to.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - What for?
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Seok Sam won.)
- I won. - I don't want to swap.
Swap with him.
- You fool! - Name a reason.
- For his sake. - Give a reason.
(The elders are fighting like kindergarten kids.)
- Fine. - Because...
- soccer players get swapped out. - Okay, yes.
(Pouting)
(The leader allows them to change places.)
- We're going this way. - Let's play.
- Let's close our eyes. - With eyes closed?
- Let's close our eyes. - We'll drop the batons, then.
(He makes up another rule again.)
- We can hold like this. - Okay.
- Eyes closed. - Eyes closed.
What is this?
(The same rules apply. Only their eyes will be closed.)
Close your eyes!
(Fumbling)
(Laughing)
(Jae Seok gets thrown down.)
(He gives chase to score a hit.)
(Flailing)
- Where is he? - Hey.
(What is this game?)
Why won't you give it over?
(The older members are totally worked up.)
What a game.
- What... - He didn't give it up.
(He lost a point because he had his eyes closed.)
It's hard with your eyes closed. We must look.
(Fool -5, North 0, Belly -4)
- Keep your eyes open. - This time...
- What? - Pass them behind our backs.
Behind our backs?
- Like this, you mean? - Like this.
(Let's pass the baton from behind our backs.)
- Like this? I like that. - Yes.
- Like this. - Behind our backs.
You're the only ones having fun.
Do you think this is break time?
- It's great fun. - It's huge fun.
- It's fun. - It's fun.
(The older members just need batons to have fun.)
Why are you having such a good time?
- The dads are having fun. - Let's not do that.
- This time... - Cham-cham-cham.
(What about...)
- Cham-cham-cham? - Then...
(They make up all kinds of rules.)
You must win to take the baton.
- Win to pass it on. - You must win.
(They can get the baton only if they win.)
- Or get hit. - Yes.
That's kind of fun.
- Someone could get both batons. - Yes.
(The Cham-cham-cham version starts.)
Let's see how it goes.
(Cham-cham-cham!)
Cham.
(He failed.)
Here.
(Smack)
- What was that? - What was that?
(He can't understand it.)
That takes too long.
- It takes too long. - Way too long.
It takes too much time.
How about we use our mouths?
I like that. That sounds like fun.
(Biting)
No way! That's gross!
(Pass it by mouth.)
(It turned into a disturbing game.)
I really don't like this.
(They're doing pretty well.)
(Smack)
In the end, it's always Seok Jin.
(Different version, same result)
- Sorry. - That was fun.
Are we the only ones having fun?
(He just realized.)
This is fun.
- This is fun. - It is.
(The older members finish with the highest satisfaction.)
- Come on. - I think it's just us.
- It is. - Right?
(Fool -5, North 0, Belly -4)
The score? Oh, okay.
- Next! - Let's go, Ji Eun.
(It is the last round.)
- Ji Hyo. - We're losing, aren't we?
(Currently -5 points)
- Totally. - We need to win, right?
- We're not in last place, though. - Ji Eun, let's go.
(Ji Hyo versus Ji Eun versus Ye Eun)
Don't worry. I'll win for us.
(The women's match between the teams)
- Don't hold back. - Do we go fast?
We'll play the song.
(Can they narrow the score gap?)
Ready, go.
(The music plays.)
Ji Eun is a grand duchess.
- Move dynamically! - Quickly.
(Oh, right.)
Why...
(Smack)
- Ji Eun! - Ji Eun.
(Slightly)
- Not like that. - Hit hard.
- Hit harder. - It doesn't hurt.
- Smack their heads off. - Okay.
Let's go.
(The game resumes.)
(Smack)
(Slightly)
Ji Eun!
- Ji Eun! - Don't be weak-hearted.
Pretend she's Jeon So Min.
- Okay. - Yes, pretend she's So Min.
(Ji Eun had no trouble taking down her college friend.)
- Okay. I got it. - Let's go!
You shouldn't move like this.
- Do this. - That's it.
- Like this. - Ji Ye Eun.
(On the beat.)
- Okay. - Ji Ye Eun.
- Vata's girlfriend! - Ji Ye Eun.
She counts two beats like this.
(Detailed)
- That's it. - Do this.
(Struggling)
We Dem Boyz!
Hey...
(Amazed)
- Not bad. - She's giving tips now?
(Ye Eun, the dancer's fiance, won't tolerate being offbeat.)
She's sensitive to rhythm.
- Okay. - I'm serious.
- That's it. - Stick to the beat.
(Let’s do this right.)
(The game resumes after a short lesson.)
- That's it. - Someone's missing the beat.
Someone's missing the beat!
(Smack)
Yes! That's it!
(Nice hit!)
Yes!
(The sergeant drills it in.)
Someone's missing the beat!
(Smacking)
That was nicely done.
(Oh, right.)
Well done. Ji Eun. Did you see that?
(Suddenly alert)
- Get a hold of yourself. - Okay.
- Ji Eun's in shock. - You need to stay alert.
This is a tough show.
She was that upset about the beat.
- One, two, three, four. - I mean...
- Okay. - Ji Eun, you need to wake up.
Ji Eun got riled up.
- One, two... - One, two, three, four.
(Ms. Ji's dance class begins.)
One, two, three, four.
(Bam!)
That's it!
One, two, three, four.
(Silence!)
- That's it! Well done! - That's it!
(Zip...)
(Feeling much better)
- You need to score. - It doesn't hurt.
(The Grand Duchess succeeded in getting her revenge.)
- Do you need more help? - Well done.
Why isn't Ji Hyo getting hit?
(As the Grand Duchess and Ms. Ji exchanged smacks...)
- Right. - She keeps winning.
(Mission 1 ends.)
- I'll announce the scores. - Okay.
After the first game, Team North has minus one point.
(The final results are announced.)
- Team North? - Yes.
- Team Belly? - Team Belly, minus five points.
- Okay. - What, us? Really?
- Not bad. - Team Fools has minus six points.
- Okay. - We won.
- Team North wins. - Unbelievable.
The Grand Duke of the North from the winning team...
will step out and choose a team.
He will then see if that team has an outsider.
- The team that came in last. - The team that came in last?
(Only the grand duke can check it.)
I mean...
This team came in last.
(Team Fools, Team North, Team Belly)
Knowing which team the outsider's on is huge.
No way.
Does the team captain keep it to himself?
(Which team will the Grand Duke of the North check for outsiders?)
I think an outsider will be on that team.
- That could be possible. - I bet...
they filmed something in advance.
Is there an outsider on Team Fools?
(Is there an outsider on Team Fools?)
(There is an outsider.)
(Team Fools, which placed last in the 1st game, has an outsider.)
- Do they know each other? - Yes.
Do the outsiders know who the other outsider is?
(That means at least one of them is an outsider.)
Yes.
- Right, I got it. - Sure.
(The Grand Duke of the North received a major clue.)
The captains should exchange information later.
- What was it? - Did you receive a hint?
Are you supposed to tell your teammates?
- You can't. - Not with your teammates.
That shouldn't be allowed.
(Except for the 3 grand dukes, everyone could be an outsider.)
Knowing there's an outsider would be a major clue.
- Did it clear things up for you? - Yes, somewhat.
(Will the Grand Duke of North be able to find an outsider?)
I wonder who it is. Who is it?
(Moving on to the next game holding the secret)
- I can't tell you. - That's it.
- Do we sit with our teams? - Yes.
- On our team... - Okay!
are two outsiders.
- Move aside. - I'm sure...
one is on Haha's team.
- No, there are two on my team. - I'm sure of it too.
(They strongly suspect the two weakest performers...)
(from the previous mission.)
I'm pretty sure it's Seok Sam.
I can bet everything I have on it.
It's been quite a while since you played a big role.
(It's been quite a while since you played a big role.)
I played one not long ago.
(He's used to being suspected like this.)
- I'm sure of it. - They gave you another one.
You got the hint, right?
(You got the hint, right?)
- I did. - Did you share with your team?
- Not yet. - Not yet?
- He shouldn't share the hint. - An outsider must be on that team.
Is there an outsider on this team, yes or no?
(Team Fools)
- That's a secret. - That's it. Nice one, SAN.
(There you go.)
Nicely done. He didn't fall for it.
(The Grand Duke of North isn't a pushover.)
- Of course. - That's it.
I'm not a spy.
You look like you belong in a military band.
- Yes, a military band. - Check it out.
(Dangling)
This next game will decide which team gets disbanded.
No!
- One team will absorb another. - That's right.
- Okay, got it. - You should do your best.
(If their team is disbanded,)
It will be exhausting to take in that team with Seok Sam.
(they're reassigned as subordinates to another team.)
We could switch teams?
(The mission that will determine the fate of the kingdom is...)
The game is called Grand Duke, Let Me Keep My Head.
(Mission 2: Grand Duke, Let Me Keep My Head)
- What's that? - It must be a quiz.
Members from each team will take turns answering.
Within three seconds,
(A word that starts with J)
they have to give a correct answer that meets the criteria.
- That seems tough. - In the process,
a grand duke from the opposing team...
(Jumping worm, Jee Seok Jin)
gets to hit someone's head for a wrong answer...
with the sponge bat.
(Bowl)
- Us? - Yes.
You lose two points for failing to provide any answer.
You lose one point if you repeat a word...
(Jumping worm)
or say one that doesn't meet the criteria.
This is going to be tough.
- Each round will be 30 seconds. - Okay.
The accumulated score determines...
- the winning team. - Got it.
Hold on a second. Ji Eun, are you empty-headed?
- Seok Jin, she finished college. - Of course.
Didn't she seem a bit empty-headed...
- when she was on the show before? - When she was on the show...
She's way above So Min.
- Yes, of course. - Compared to So Min?
- She's way above So Min. - Yes, compared to So Min...
(We're excited to see what So Bal's friend Ji Eun can do.)
- So Min's tough to beat. - Exactly.
The playing order is as follows.
(The team taking on the challenge in Round 1 is...)
- We'll start with Team Fools. - Okay.
(Team Fools.)
- One of them is an outsider. - No way.
(Team Fools finished last in the mission,)
- Among the dukes... - Absolutely not.
(making them the prime suspect for having an outsider.)
Look at how Seok Jin is sitting.
- Seok Jin, what's with that pose? - Why are you sitting like that?
- Well... - Are you nervous?
(Polite)
How should I sit? Just how?
Like this?
- Just sit comfortably. - How should I sit? This is normal.
- That's just weird. - I haven't seen anyone...
- sit like that on the show before. - It's weird.
- What's wrong with it? - He was like this.
(Is Seok Sam, who is unusually polite, really an outsider?)
- Anyway, move. - He's definitely up to something.
(Looking intently)
He must be fulfilling some sort of mission.
- All right. - Here we go.
(With all eyes on them, Team Fools begin the mission.)
- Start with Haha. - Me?
- Haha or Seok Jin? - It doesn't matter.
(They start with Seok Sam.)
- I'll go first. Okay. - Get ready.
Name a Korean proverb that features an animal.
One, two, three.
- Frog. - Three...
- Dog... - One, two, three.
Speak of the devil.
- One, two, three. - A well-behaved cat...
- One, two, three. - I was giving my answer.
- One, two, three. - The day has eyes,
- the night has ears. - That's it.
(Duke Ha is doing better than expected.)
- One, two, three. - Crows fly, and the pear falls.
- One, two, three. - A tiger doesn't fear a tiger.
- What? - A tiger doesn't fear a tiger.
- What? - A tiger doesn't fear it?
A tiger doesn't fear a tiger?
(Laughing)
- A pup doesn't fear a tiger. - A pup doesn't fear a tiger.
(It's a pup, not a tiger.)
"Horangi" and "beom" both mean tiger.
"Horangi" and "beom" are the same thing.
(A tiger doesn't fear a tiger?)
"Beom" is a tiger too.
(Time is up.)
Your time is up.
A tiger doesn't fear a tiger? What does that mean?
She finally figured out what was wrong with it.
"Horangi" and "beom" are the same thing.
(Embarrassed)
What was that?
- You should've done better. - That was weird.
- They did poorly. - Hold on.
- A tiger doesn't fear a tiger? - What was that?
(Her bizarre answer immediately made them suspect her.)
- They're the same thing. - She...
- Ye Eun. - Like I said, she's not ordinary.
(Is Ji Eun an outsider as Haha thinks?)
- That's not it. - Get a grip on yourself.
- SAN, Ye Eun, - It's really not me.
(Next up is Team North.)
- stay on your toes. - It's really not me.
- You know proverbs, right? - It's really not me.
(I'm really not an outsider.)
Seriously. Jae Seok, I've spent...
- my whole life singing and dancing. - It might not be proverbs.
It's okay. SAN, play with confidence.
- Confidence. - Yes, confidence.
(The duke is a singing and dancing expert.)
- Confidence. - Confidence.
- Should I do it? - Oh, no.
(How good will he be at quizzes?)
- Get ready. - Sure.
(The question for Team North is revealed.)
- Here we go. - This isn't easy.
Name scientists. One, two, three.
- Einstein. - One, two, three.
- One, two, three. - Sorry.
- One, two, three. - Schubert.
(Composer)
- Schubert. - One...
- Sorry. - One, two, three.
(The team has two weak links.)
- Schubert. - Schubert?
- One, two, three. - Pasteur.
- One, two, three. - I can't think of anyone.
- One, two, three. - Jang Yeong Sil.
- One, two, three. - Newton.
One, two, three.
- Sorry. - Seriously?
Madame Aema.
- One, two, three. - Roentgen.
(German physicist Roentgen)
One, two, three.
- Roentgen. - One, two, three.
Seriously, SAN?
- One, two, three. - Marie Curie.
(Not the protagonist of a famous movie)
SAN, that's how you do it.
(Time is up.)
- Are you kidding me? - What...
- Yes! - I mean...
(Sorry)
- Are you kidding me? - We did better.
- Are you kidding me with Schubert? - What's wrong with you?
(The King of Lieder)
SAN, what on earth was that?
Seriously, what happened?
- Schubert? - I didn't know anyone.
(You're a problem too.)
Tell me about it.
Schubert?
- Scientists were hard to name. - That was too hard.
(Ddochi got two answers right, but SAN couldn't even say anything.)
How delicious.
SAN kept apologizing over and over again.
(The Grand Duke of North really showed his human side.)
- Scientists were hard to name. - What did he do that was wrong?
- That was tough. - It's tough...
(Next is Team Belly.)
- when you're on the spot. - Get ready.
- Give us an easy one. - Here we go.
- Name some economic jargon. - Nice.
- One, two, three. - The Veblen Effect.
(Increasing demand despite rising prices)
- One, two, three. - Engel's index.
(Share of food spending in total expenditure)
- One, two, three. - Inflation.
(Rising prices)
- One, two, three. - Gray Elephant.
One, two...
(A gray rhino is a predictable but easily overlooked risk.)
- Incorrect. - It's a rhino.
- One, two, three. - IMF.
(International Monetary Fund)
- One, two, three. - Deflation.
(Falling prices)
(The Empty Head Siblings are doing well.)
- Why are they so good? - It's different from inflation.
- They're different. - Got it.
(Smug)
- One, two, three. - Stagflation.
(The economy stagnates while prices rise.)
- One, two, three. - Well...
Incorrect. One, two, three.
- SK Hynix. - What?
(Yang Empty Head has nothing left to say.)
That was funny.
One, two, three.
- One, two, three. - Shrink.
- Shrink. - Yes, shrink.
- And? - Something's attached to that.
- Shrink... - Shrinkflation.
(Same price, less product)
- Nice. - She got it.
- One, two, three. - Samsung Electronics.
(Another market leader)
- One, two, three. - Are we not done?
- One, two, three. - I thought we were done.
- One, two, three. - Isn't our time up?
- One, two, three. - Tesla.
- It's over. - Tesla.
- I thought our time was up. - Seriously.
(He expanded into the US market.)
(The round ends with him giving market leaders a shoutout.)
- Mr. Empty Head. - We're doomed! Oh, no.
- That was hilarious. - You guys lost for sure.
(Team Fools will start again.)
Starting with Haha, name some painters.
- One, two, three. - Gogh.
One, two, three. Incorrect.
- One, two, three. - Picasso.
- One, two, three. - Lee Hoon Young.
- Who's Lee Hoon Young? - Darn.
Arsatato.
- One, two... - P...
(Team Fools ended up playing whack-a-mole.)
One, two, three.
- One, two, three. - Beast.
(Four-syllable Chinese idioms)
- One, two, three. - Gojingamrae.
- One, two, three. - Washinsangdam.
- One, two, three. - Meeinyangchu.
- One, two, three. - Ilseokyijo.
- One, two, three. - Ilgeoyangdeuk.
- One, two, three. - Jintoeyangnan.
- He's good at this. - One, two, three.
- I think I did a pretty good job. - You did.
(SAN did pretty well on the four-syllable idiom questions.)
You redeemed yourself in that last round.
Nice. I don't think we'll be disbanded.
(The final result is announced.)
- I think it'll be between them. - It was probably close.
- It was close. - That was tough.
Here's the result. All right.
(The losing team will be disabanded immediately.)
Team North, minus 29 points.
- What? - That's a lot.
Team Belly, minus 28 points.
- No way. - Team Fools...
Our team must be getting absorbed.
(Nervous)
Team Fools,
- minus 43 points. - What?
- Us? - Minus 43 points.
(Team Fools finished last.)
- Us? - How so?
- They got a lot wrong. - You did poorly.
- Especially Ji Eun. - You got a lot wrong.
(Laughing)
- They're getting disbanded. - You got a lot wrong.
(Just like in the previous mission, Ji Eun cost her team many points.)
Is it really 26 versus 43?
We got minus 43 points?
I'm sorry. Apparently, it's all my fault.
Team Fools is disbanded.
- Disbanded! - Us?
(The fall of the Grand Duke of Fools' domain)
- Do we get absorbed? - They need to join our teams.
Yes, the winners, Team Belly,
(Benefits for Team Belly, the winning team)
will get a chance to take a teammate.
(Se Chan, the Grand Duke of Belly, can pick a subject to recruit.)
I'm sorry, but isn't it better to leave the spy behind?
(Suspecting Ji Eun)
This will only confuse SAN.
(Only SAN knows that Team Fools has an outsider.)
- But he knows. - We should just take him.
- Yes, I know. - We'll help.
You don't know who it is though.
(At least one of Ji Eun and Seok Sam has to be an outsider.)
Exactly. That'll only confuse you.
You should decide after discussing it with him.
Can the grand dukes discuss this first?
- Sure thing. - Go for it.
(The grand dukes hold a meeting to identify the outsider.)
- SAN, nice. - Come here.
- Bad-to-worse. - What?
What was your hint?
- Come here. They'll hear us. - First...
- Yes or no? - There's one on your team.
(The Grand Duke of Fools)
- Of course. - Us? Yes.
(He shares the hint he got.)
How many are on my team?
I only know that there's an outsider on your team.
(He doesn't know how many outsiders there are.)
- Is that it? - That's all I was told.
Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, can you come over here?
- Yes, get over here. - You're taking too long.
(They call Team Belly, the winning team.)
- Do you think it's not them? - Seriously.
Since we won,
- we can choose a teammate. - That's right.
We can play it safe...
- and just take Haha. - But...
- We're taking Haha for sure. - I see.
(There are no outsiders among the grand dukes.)
- I'm suspicious of Ji Eun. - Ji Eun.
- Ji Eun? - I'm sure of it.
Ji Eun...
(Ji Eun is the prime suspect for being an outsider.)
- We won't take her. - We won't take her.
- What if we take Seok Jin... - Let's make that team clean.
(They decide it'd be better not to bring in Ji Eun.)
If they take Seok Jin...
It's not me!
- Seok Jin doesn't seem like it. - I don't think he is.
(Seok Jin did his best.)
- He did his best. - He did his best.
(Thinking)
- We could also take Seok Jin... - I...
If Seok Jin and I...
- Why? - join that team...
What is it? You think he is?
- I think Seok Jin is also... - Seok Jin is also...
- an outsider. - That's what you think?
- Two in our team? - I see.
I think he's imitating someone.
- I had a feeling. - You had a feeling.
(Did Seok Sam keep behaving suspiciously?)
He's imitating someone?
- Someone imitated you earlier. - That's why...
He imitated things like this.
He suddenly did this pose.
(SAN's deduction: He copied the moves...)
- He normally doesn't do it. - That's right.
(and was sitting with his legs apart, which is suspicious.)
He suddenly sat like this.
You've become quite sharp.
- It really makes sense. - So I think...
that's the hidden mission.
- Imitating someone. - Imitating a certain person.
We have to separate Seok Jin and Ji Eun.
(They decide to split the two suspects between the teams.)
- We have to separate them. - Okay.
- Since it's confusing. - Yes, since it's confusing.
- Then let's take Haha. - Yes. Let's take Haha.
What about those two?
Let's send Ji Eun to that team.
(The Grand Duke of Belly's strategy)
- We can take Seok Jin as well. - Let's do that.
(They'll send Ji Eun to Team North and bring Seok Sam to their team.)
It's so hard.
(They decided who to recruit.)
- It's hard. - It's so hard.
- Jae Seok. - We can't...
SAN...
- came back changed. - Why do you say that?
Now that he's doing well, he's sharp.
Seriously. He...
(He doesn't know what to do.)
He's very observant.
(The results of the grand dukes' meeting are announced.)
First,
- we'll bring Haha, who's safe. - Yes.
And...
- Ji Eun and Seok Jin... - Us?
(Among Ji Eun and Seok Sam, suspects for being outsiders)
SAN said there's an outsider in their team. Considering that...
(SAN suspects Seok Sam, and Se Chan suspects Ji Eun.)
Ji Eun's tiger thing was suspicious.
(Ji Eun, the prime suspect, will be sent to Team North.)
- "Horangi" and "beom". - Yes.
We'll take in Seok Jin as well.
(Grand Duke of North: Ji Eun, Grand Duke of Belly: Seok Jin)
- Seok Jin and I'll be joining. - Come.
(They were absorbed into the other teams.)
We have to put them in that team.
- We're going to head out to eat. - Yes.
Before we leave,
the prize money that the Grand Duke of the Fools had...
(The Grand Duke of Fools have 100 dollars.)
will go to the Grand Duke of the Belly that won first place.
(The Grand Duke of Belly, the winner, will confiscate it.)
- I don't have it. - You don't?
(I don't have the prize envelope.)
- Seok Jin is sitting on it. - You're sitting on it.
(What?)
I sat on it. Well...
(Turning himself in right away)
- You can try and take it. - Should I pull down your pants?
Why did you take that?
I took it because it was there. Why?
(Shameless)
Why are you stealing?
- Grandpa. - Why did you take that?
(Everything he does is suspicious.)
Can't I take it?
- People took from me all my life. - It's not...
(Suddenly mad)
- They're taking it back. - Right.
(Keeping an eye on him)
- We have 300 dollars then. - Also,
the members of Team Fools will dress up as beggars...
- since they fell apart. - Right.
Why are you doing this?
(It's a fitting punishment for the people of a fallen kingdom.)
- You should become beggars. - It's time they did that.
- Beggars! - They're way too comfortable.
She went to the salon at 6am.
- That's what makes it funny. - Yes.
- I appeared as a princess. - A princess.
- She started off as a princess, - Okay.
(A full beggar set)
and now she's a beggar.
- Come on. - Goodness.
(It's been a long time.)
- Seok Sam looks good in it. - I'm...
- Your body remembers it. - Yes. Just do it.
(Changing clothes with ease)
(His body remembers the beggar look.)
- Seok Jin looks good. - As expected.
- As expected. - It's something that suits him.
(Jee Seok Sam, the master of beggar disguises)
It suits you perfectly.
As expected.
It's nice, Seok Jin. You have more hair.
You're suited to be a beggar.
(While Beggar Seok Sam finds his true self)
He's really good at dressing up.
- You should do that much. - Help me with this.
(The grand duchess is unfamiliar with variety-show makeup.)
- Just draw some snot. - How do I draw it?
Please do it for me.
(Grand Duke Yang, the expert, appears.)
(Focusing)
I'm getting worried.
- It's me. - It's...
I did this my whole life.
(Trust me.)
I feel nervous.
It's too... Who did this to Ji Eun's face?
Why didn't you draw some snot on her?
(Beggar Ji Eun is here.)
You should have kept it reasonable.
We can't see her face.
(In his hands, she was reborn as a variety show star.)
- You should've kept it reasonable. - I drew the snot.
Do I look bad? How do I look?
It doesn't look bad.
- Doesn't she look cute? - What is this?
He painted her whole face.
- Let me see. - He likes her!
It's cute.
- He likes her! - It's cute.
(Grinning)
You should put more.
He likes her too.
- What is this? - It's okay.
Se Chan likes her.
- You should give her... - Do you like Ji Eun?
- He likes her. - I don't like her.
He likes her.
- Who puts makeup like that? - Se Chan!
- When you're with Ye Eun, you... - Seriously.
(Satisfied)
Why are people from Dongduk Women's University so cute?
(Another cutie from Dongduk Women's University)
Why am I attracted to people from Dongduk Women's University?
- Why is that? - He likes her.
(Grand Duke Yang is drawn to the fallen grand duchess.)
- He likes her. - There's something there.
He likes Ji Eun.
We're going to head out to eat.
We arranged a pasta place...
(Today's lunch picked by the grand dukes)
that suits the Grand Duke...
(The grand dukes' main dish, pasta)
and a barbecue restaurant that you like.
(Meat, which is everyone's favorite)
Team Belly who won will choose the restaurant first.
(The Grand Duke of Belly will pick first.)
- Let's go with meat. - Meat? Yes. Se Chan...
(He chooses meat.)
Why meat? It takes a long time.
- Meat. - He wants us to eat meat.
Team North will have pasta.
(Automatically, Team North will have pasta.)
- Nice. Pasta is nice. - I love it.
We're going to give you some cards.
The five cards here...
have amounts starting from 10 dollars to 150 dollars.
You can pick one card from here.
You can spend up to the amount on the card...
on your meal.
The Grand Duke of the Belly can pick a card first.
Which card should I go with?
- What does your gut feeling say? - Why think?
Don't pick it.
- You touched that. - You're done.
(Touching)
It's over once he picks it up.
- He didn't pick it up. - It's over once you pick it up.
I didn't pick it up.
(Childish)
- It's over once you pick it up. - What's wrong with your eyes?
- I didn't pick it up. - It's over once you pick it up.
(They argue like kindergarteners again.)
- I didn't pick it up. I touched it. - It's over once you pick it up.
- It's over once you pick it up. - That doesn't look good.
- The yellow one... - This one...
(They calm down and start selecting again.)
(Number 2)
What about this?
- Right. - It's cute.
It doesn't have much hair like Seok Jin.
(The character doesn't have much hair like Seok Jin.)
But...
- Number two. - Grand Duke.
You're giving a beggar too much power.
- Why is a beggar doing everything? - Exactly.
- The beggar... - Step back.
I can give my opinion.
You're giving a beggar too much power.
(He chooses number 2 as Seok Sam said.)
I won't give him food later.
(Next is the Grand Duke of North.)
- This is so hard. - SAN.
- Choose the one you want. - The yellow one.
His shoulders look great.
- Right. - I...
- will pick the black card. - Okay.
(He picks number 1, the black card.)
- It's neat. - Good.
The two teams will split up...
(How much money did they choose?)
- That's a good one. - and head out to eat.
Yes.
- There's a park. - It's raining.
(The grand dukes and the townspeople are walking down the rainy street.)
- It's raining. - Where do we go?
Grand Duke.
(She's the only beggar.)
Se Chan went easy on you.
The snot needs to start here.
(Nagging)
- Where... - It's starting from the side.
It's going to the side.
- You look pretty right now. - Right.
- He didn't paint the top. - Right.
I feel lonely.
I've joined another team...
dressed like this.
You're the only one dressed up like that.
(Feeling sad)
The beggars are here.
(Her beggar colleagues join them.)
- Ji Eun. - Yes?
Do you...
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't.
What do you think about Se Chan?
(Straight to the point)
I'll stay without one.
(Firm)
I should stop getting involved with...
- Dongduk Women's University people. - Of course.
Who do you think is too good for the other?
(He got involved with her in 1 second.)
- What? - Who's too good for the other?
- It's okay. - He doesn't even need to say it.
Who's too good for the other, Ye Eun?
I don't even need to say it.
Let's go.
(Petty)
Vata is too good for you too!
Seriously.
(While Grand Duke Yang's romance got wrecked,)
What's this place? We're here.
(Team North arrived at the restaurant.)
- It's this place. - Pasta.
Nice.
This is nice. We don't have to grill the meat.
(Excited)
- You can sit first. - Yes.
(Your Grace)
- The grand duke can come here. - grand duke.
(The grand duke sits in the middle.)
The grand duke can enter first.
- You're not on our team, so... - Ji Eun can sit at the end.
- You're not on our team. - Yes.
We're on the same team now.
- We're on the same team now. - Aren't we on the same team now?
- That's right. - We're on the same team now.
(The grand duchess' somewhat rough adjustment to her new country)
We're on the same team now.
Yes. I'll do my best.
We're going to give you the menu.
Yes.
(Springing)
- As we told you... - Give it to us.
I should be sitting at the end.
- Come on, SAN. - I'm sorry.
(Enjoy it.)
- You're a grand duke today. - The grand duke.
(The K-youngest isn't comfortable being the grand duke.)
You can order within the card limit.
- Yes. - If it goes over the limit,
you can make another payment.
How much would it have?
It would be troublesome if it only has ten dollars.
(The card limit is randomly set between 10 dollars and 150 dollars.)
- We won't be able to get anything. - I have a feeling...
there's a lot of money on it.
What would you like to eat?
- I think oil pasta would be great. - Right.
(Oil pasta, 17 dollars)
- It looks nice. - We also need rice,
(Salivating)
so pilaf would be good.
(Pilaf, 17 dollars)
- Nice. - Pilaf.
Shall we also get French toast?
(French toast, 17 dollars)
- That would be nice. - I want French toast.
(Laughing)
- Ye Eun. - Yes.
You said you were tired of pasta because you had it...
(The grand duke and the townspeople are excited to feast.)
for two days in a row.
- Are you all right with it? - Yes. I'm a bit European.
What would you like to have?
(To Ji Eun)
Can I pick one?
(Oh, right)
No. We will...
(He forgot her status for a moment.)
You can't pick.
- Then just pick one. - Okay.
(He pities her.)
- Just one dish. - Nothing expensive.
- We ordered pasta, - Pasta.
(She barely got a choice.)
- a toast... - That's right.
- Let's get a steak. - We should have steak.
(Steak, 34 dollars)
- Steak. - Hey...
Steak?
(Dumbfounded)
If it doesn't work, we can take this one out first.
Okay. Hold on.
- Steak... - How much is the steak?
Which pilaf should we get?
She really has no shame.
(Checking the price)
(She won't give up even though she's fallen from grace.)
We came here to get pasta.
She chose a 200g tenderloin steak that's 33 dollars.
- Shall we make the order then? - Okay.
Which pilaf do you like?
Then...
Pork shoulder?
What? Pork shoulder?
(Her love for meat knows no bounds.)
From the right side, I keep hearing her say,
"Pork shoulder? Steak?"
- Since she's on a diet, - "Pasta?"
(She watches the room but still says what she wants to say.)
she's trying to avoid having carbohydrates.
Then we'll have...
one pollack roe oil pasta...
What pasta did you say you were going to have?
It was the pollack roe pasta...
but with cream.
You want to go with cream? Okay.
But I like tomato pasta too.
Can we order three?
(She's delighted to hear they're ordering 3 pastas.)
We have to have the pollack roe oil pasta.
We could get them all if we have 150 dollars.
- That's right. It would be enough. - If it doesn't have 150 dollars,
(They assume they got 150 dollars...)
- we can't get anything with ten. - Okay.
- Okay. - Let's order three pastas.
(and order everything they want.)
- Grand Duke. - What will it be?
What will it be?
(He's going to order before paying.)
We'll get...
one French toast,
- pollack roe oil pasta, - Yes.
seafood tomato pasta,
pork shoulder pilaf,
and tenderloin steak.
We'll order those.
If the payment doesn't go through,
start by removing the steak.
Okay.
The total is 102 dollars.
It's 102 dollars.
Right. It should be enough.
(With a 150-dollar limit, they still have plenty of room to spend.)
- It's enough. - We have a chance.
- If we can make that payment, - If it doesn't go through...
- then... - More!
- More! - Coffee.
(They're excited at the thought of ordering more.)
- Coffee and Coke. - That's right.
- Coke? - Coke and coffee.
- We should have those. - I'll process the payment.
(Did the Grand Duke of the North pick the card with 150 dollars?)
Okay.
- Please. - Can I get some water?
(Employee)
- Please sign here. - Please.
- Did it work? - I have to sign.
(Did the transaction go through?)
I have to sign.
Or will we know after I sign?
- It didn't work yet. - Please.
- Please sign. - Or will we know after I sign?
(He signed as well.)
(What will be the result?)
Please.
(Will Ji Eun get to eat the steak?)
Please. No.
(102 dollars: Card limit exceeded)
The payment was declined.
No.
It didn't go through.
- Should I remove the steak? - Remove the steak.
- Remove the steak first. - I'll remove the steak.
(Flying fish roe pasta: 17 dollars, tomato pasta: 17 dollars)
But what if we keep removing dishes, and it turns out...
(French toast: 17 dollars, pilaf: 17 dollars, steak: 34 dollars)
- to have 10 dollars? - Does it have 10 dollars?
If there's ten dollars, coming here would be a mistake.
(68 dollars in total)
- It's 68 dollars now. - It's 68 dollars.
(Please)
Please. At least those...
I'm at the signing stage.
(Will the transaction go through this time?)
We don't sign when the total is under 50 dollars, right?
- The payment was declined. - It's over the card limit.
(68 dollars: Card limit exceeded)
It's over the card limit.
- Again? - What?
What?
(No)
- We should remove the pilaf. - Remove the pilaf.
Pilaf?
(Flying fish roe pasta: 17 dollars, tomato pasta: 17 dollars)
- The card limit is too low. - Remove the pilaf.
(French toast: 17 dollars)
- That will be 51 dollars. - What if the balance is 50 dollars?
(They try paying 51 dollars.)
Would drawing a heart help?
This needs to go through. It just has to.
(Will his heartfelt transaction go through?)
- The payment was declined. - It was declined.
(51 dollars: Card limit exceeded)
It was declined.
(Payment declined and confirmed)
(Stunned)
- This is bad. - Remove the French toast.
- Remove the French toast. - The toast.
(Flying fish roe pasta: 17 dollars, tomato pasta: 17 dollars)
- We won't order the toast. - I mean...
Why did we even come here?
(The total is now 34 dollars.)
- I'm hungry. - Could the balance be ten dollars?
(Please)
Ten dollars is the absolute worst.
- The payment was declined. - For real?
(34 dollars: Card limit exceeded)
- For real? It was declined. - What?
- It must be ten dollars. - Was it declined again?
- No way. - Is this for real?
Remove everything except the fish roe pasta.
(Making a decision)
- The fish roe pasta. - Remove everything...
(In the end, only 1 17-dollar dish is left.)
except the fish roe oil pasta.
- If this doesn't go through... - The flying fish roe pasta...
(If the transaction fails again, they'll have nothing to eat.)
- is 17 dollars. - What...
Can't I pay for this myself?
(Can they at least eat some pasta?)
Please...
- Transaction complete. - It worked.
(17 dollars: Payment successful)
It worked.
(They were able to order the flying fish roe pasta.)
Can't we know how much is left?
Did we only order the fish roe dish?
- Yes. - Why don't we order one more?
- Yes, one more. - Let's order the toast.
(The French toast that failed to go through)
The French toast is 17 dollars.
I see, 17 dollars.
Since 34 dollars was declined...
- Is it 30 dollars? - but 17 dollars was approved,
the limit might be 30 dollars.
- That must be it. - Yes, it must be 30 dollars.
Let's order something that's 13 dollars.
Coffee or something like that?
(They spring to their feet at the news that they can order more.)
What dishes do they have?
Ji Eun, get back in your seat.
I was only getting us some water.
We could order four baskets of this bread and cheese.
(Bread and cheese, 3 dollars)
Right?
- Let's give it a try. - Should I?
(They agreed to pay an extra 12 dollars, as Food Fighter suggested.)
I think we'll have at least 12 dollars to spend.
- We should have some bread. - Four bread and cheese, please.
(If this works, they can each have some bread.)
We should have some bread.
Four bread and cheese, please.
(She doesn't forget to take the water.)
Yes, four of these.
(Holding tightly)
Please... Can we afford this?
We can't work on an empty stomach.
(Trying to pay 12 dollars)
Will this work?
(Will he be able to feed his people?)
- Please... - Please let this work.
Please...
Please let this work.
(Payment successful)
- Transaction complete. - Hey, it worked.
- The limit must be 30 dollars. - It must be 30 dollars.
(4 3-dollar pieces of bread survived.)
How much did we spend?
(Happy)
- Is it 12 dollars? - We...
- We have a dollar left. - A dollar?
(They paid 29 dollars in total.)
You don't have anything for one dollar, right?
Could we get some more noodles?
(Winking)
- If you can, please. - Ma'am.
They have beverages.
- But nothing is for a dollar. - One serving that looks like four.
- Like japchae... - Like four servings.
We'd like a big dish like japchae.
(Being hungry, they lobby the owner.)
- One serving that looks like four. - Japchae pasta.
(Meanwhile, Ji Eun is fully commited to playing the role of a beggar.)
- Ji Eun. - Yes?
- Sorry about this. - I've got this. Please sit.
- No, let me. - It's all right.
(Polite)
- A senior shouldn't do this. - It's okay.
- Ji Eun. - Please have a seat.
- It's just that Ji Eun... - I mean...
is the beggar right now.
- I should do this. - Right.
- Grand Duke, please have a seat. - It's...
- Let me. - Grand Duke, please have a seat.
(The polite grand duke is sent away.)
Ji Eun, here.
(She's playing the character again.)
That's enough.
- I'll enjoy. - Over there.
- We ordered four bread, - Right.
so have your fill.
We have strict social classes, so I was taken aback earlier.
(She's still hung up on the steak.)
Even the grand duke is eating a dish that's only 17 dollars.
I wonder what the other team's limit is.
Unbelievable.
(Team Belly in the meantime)
- Goodness. - We should check the menu.
(They're checking the menu.)
Let's take a look at the price range.
The five-person combo looks good.
(Immediately)
- How are we a 5-person team? - It's only 4.
(5-person, 4-person, 3-person)
(He rebels against the unfair treatment.)
- How are we a five-person team? - Look.
I mean...
Don't you dare lay a hand on our grand duke again.
(Kissing up to the grand duke)
- Got it. - What will it be?
(Obedient)
- The 4-person combo is 58 dollars, - Okay.
(5-person combo: 77 dollars, 4-person combo: 58 dollars)
but the 5-person combo is 77 dollars.
- Yes, 77. - What will it be?
- Go with the five-person combo? - That's my opinion.
- How about this? - We'll start with the 5-person...
(They'll try paying for the 5-person combo 1st.)
- and go down if needed. - We'll go to the 4-person combo.
- Sure. - It's not like...
we'll lose ten dollars for every attempt.
If the payment is denied for the five-person combo,
you won't get to eat anything.
- Are you sure about this? - Of course.
I can grill this hair instead.
- You'll grill it? - Isn't that what you meant?
He said you were going to starve.
(Starving, not grilling)
- You're going to starve. - I see.
- I can't have that. - If we fail, I mean.
(I can't starve.)
How could that be so hard to understand?
I thought he was telling me to do the grilling.
(Embarrassed)
I'll give it a try.
(Grand Duke Yang will try paying.)
- Let's give it a try. - Start with the 5-person combo...
- and go down from there. - Right.
We'll go with the 77 dollars.
(He tries paying 77 dollars for the 5-person combo.)
- The 77 dollars? - Yes.
- The 5-person combo. - The 5-person combo.
I hope it goes through on the first try.
- Let's do this. Let's eat. - Let's go.
(Will they get lucky on the first try?)
Signature, transaction complete.
(Please)
I'm on the luckier side.
The payment was declined.
(77 dollars: Card limit exceeded)
- Transaction complete. - The payment was declined.
Card limit exceeded. We were expecting that.
- It's over the limit. - Go with the four-person combo.
(They switches to the 4-person combo, which is 58 dollars.)
- Now... - The four-person combo.
If there isn't enough for 77 dollars,
- it's going to be... - Go with the four-person combo.
We'll have to afford at least 50-something dollars.
(They need to have more than 58 dollars to pay.)
But there's a good chance that'll exceed the limit too.
- You never know. - The four-person combo.
(He tries paying 58 dollars for the 4-person combo.)
- The four-person combo. Let's go. - The 58 dollars.
- Okay, 58 dollars. - The limit could be 70 dollars.
Please let this go through.
- The payment was declined. - Nice!
(58 dollars: Card limit exceeded)
- Is it done? - No?
It's over the card limit.
- Darn. - Are you kidding me?
- Go with the 3-person combo. - The 3-person combo.
(They switches to the 3-person combo, which is 44 dollars.)
- The 3-person combo. - The limit must be 50 dollars.
- Seriously? - Let's have at least us three eat.
Let's have at least the three of us eat.
What if the limit is 20 dollars?
We picked the wrong credit card.
Can I at least order the silken tofu ramyeon?
(Meanwhile)
Getting the 3-person combo comes first. Okay, 44 dollars.
I told you to get the yellow card.
- Transaction complete. - It went through.
(44 dollars: Payment successful)
(They at least got the 3-person combo.)
- Hold on. - The silken tofu ramyeon.
- Since 44 dollars went through... - It must be 50 dollars.
- It must be 50 dollars. - I think the limit is 50 dollars.
- We have three portions of meat. - The doenjang sulbap.
(If the limit is 50 dollars, they can spend an extra 6 dollars.)
- How about ramyeon? - The silken tofu ramyeon, please.
- Let's get the doenjang sulbap. - The ramyeon is five dollars.
(Doenjang sulbap, 6 dollars)
- One ramyeon and one bowl of rice. - And a bowl of rice.
(Ignoring)
- Why is it up to you? - Doenjang sulbap...
- Jong Kook, the bowl of rice... - Isn't ramyeon the better option?
(Ignoring again)
Let's order the doenjang sulbap.
- Wait, listen to this. - Yes, that's better.
- We got the three-person combo, - We can't take back the order.
- but there are five people here. - Sure.
We should at least order two bowls of rice.
- How are there five mouths to feed? - It's like this.
- There are 3 people, and 2 beggars. - Mister, get back here.
Just order the doenjang sulbap then.
(Doenjang sulbap, 6 dollars)
We should just share the doenjang sulbap.
(They still pick doenjang sulbap, which is Seok Sam's favorite.)
- Sure. - That's not bad.
- The sulbap is a good choice. - Let's go with that.
How many people does the doenjang sulbap serve?
- Probably 1. - It's 1 serving.
(Employee)
- Is it only one serving? Come on. - That's...
Then that won't be enough.
(They ignore Seok Jin and try to order the 6-dollar doenjang sulbap.)
- The limit is 50 dollars. - Yes, 50 dollars.
- Fifty dollars, right? - Transaction complete.
(Payment successful)
- There. - It was 50 dollars.
- That's better than most. Good job. - I made a good choice.
(They paid 50 dollars for the 3-person combo and sulbap.)
- We'll set the table over here. - Right.
You can set the table for the meat right here.
- Thank you. - That looks good.
(The meat is served first.)
- That looks good. - No way.
(The 3-person combo that's enough for 3 people)
- Check this out. - That's quality meat.
Check this out. This comes with...
(Satisfied)
- a lot of side dishes. - No way.
Seok Jin, let's fire ours up too.
Yes, let's do that. You never know.
Why are you firing it up? What for?
Bean sprouts!
- Sure. - Bean sprouts? Sure thing.
- Look here, Mr. Kim. - What is it, Mr. Jee?
- Aren't we in the same shoes? - How so?
If that were the case, I'd be wearing that outfit too.
(He's right.)
(Their outfits show the difference in their status.)
- What? - This is a fashion statement.
- We wore this to be stylish. - How are we the same...
when you're dressed as beggars?
- Call me Pumba. - Hey...
- I'm not a beggar. - Pumba?
Your Grace.
- That sound is incredible. - Can't we have one of them?
- I won't ask for more. - Perfect timing.
(Beggar Ha starts begging.)
What do you mean you won't ask for more?
(Suddenly)
- Seriously? - Hey, mister!
(Just one piece)
Just the smaller piece.
- No way. - Are you kidding me?
We'll cook it on just one of the grills.
- There's more than enough. - Why waste this grill?
We'll think about giving you some later.
Turn it off then. Why are you wasting gas?
I'll grill the kimchi for you.
(He volunteers to grill the kimchi.)
- Okay, hurry up with that. - Hold on.
If you give us some pork fat...
(Casually)
You know you can't cook with that on this grill.
- We'll put on a show for you. - We'll cook it on...
- just one of the grills. - How about some whistling?
Shouldn't you know that since you run a barbecue place?
(A sudden whistling performance)
(Embarrassed)
(Chuckling)
- Why... - Do you know why we did that?
We're thinking about releasing an album.
The Whistling Boys.
(Whistling Boys, the beggar duo)
We're thinking about releasing an album as the Whistling Boys.
Can you do a song for us?
- Of course. - Any requests?
(Of course we can do it.)
- How about "One Man?" - Okay, go.
("One Man" by Whistling Boys, original song by Kim Jong Kook)
(The original singer is pleased.)
They're pretty good.
(A pretty pleasant begging show)
They're good.
If only this were actually useful.
(The beggars even add harmony.)
(Laughing)
(An angelic melody pours from their puckered lips.)
(Give us a piece.)
(Impressed)
- We should thank them. - No way. That...
- Thank you. Hold on. - Thank you. Ready, go.
(Even the "thank you" is perfect.)
(Satisfied)
You should give us something for that.
- There's more than enough. - We'll grill this first.
- Seriously, mister. - We even performed for you.
- That cost us our jaws. - We got you. Just be patient.
The meat isn't ready yet.
Why do you keep insisting when the meat isn't cooked?
(They resume performing after hearing they'll get some meat.)
I'm sorry, but it's annoying now.
(Hurt)
Give them some meat and send them on their way.
Let us have one of the cuts.
- Hey. - Hey.
How many pieces do you want each?
(Pitiful)
- Three. - Go ahead. Let's hear it.
- Three. - He wants three pieces.
(The deal broke down because of their unreasonable demand.)
Are you kidding me?
(The pork belly is cooked.)
We'll try the meat that's been cooked...
and see how good it is.
You're going to eat it?
- Well... - When the beggars...
(They start eating without the Whistling Brothers.)
are left here watching?
- That's just mean. - Seriously.
- That's why... - What they're doing is mean.
- The ssamjang... - Let us have a piece.
(Exclaiming)
Hold on. Let us try some first.
- It's good. - I'll see if it's good.
(Savoring)
It's so good.
(Impressed)
(They get a piece for providing entertainment.)
(Pulling)
(The good brothers even share a piece of meat.)
Thank you.
(Exclaiming)
Oh my gosh.
(Automatic whistling)
(Fumbling)
Now that I'm eating, I can't do it properly.
That tasted amazing.
I'll have some of the doenjang sulbap.
Sure.
(Stealing a piece of paradise)
Can we have the sulbap?
Here.
I saw Seok Jin...
steal a piece of meat just now.
(Trying to look away)
Grand Duke Haha,
sit with us.
(The Grand Duke of the Belly strictly rewards and punishes.)
Have as much as you want.
Sit with us. Have as much as you want.
(Beggar Ha leaves his guilty brother behind.)
I have to address this. Enjoy the sulbap too.
- What? - Do you want some?
Stop it. You're done.
- Hey. - Haha, enjoy.
- Hey. - I can't believe you.
- Have you no pride at all? - No.
(He takes it out on Haha instead.)
I can't believe you just joined them.
- Have as much as you want. - Thank you!
(Loyal)
- I warned you, didn't I? - Good job.
(The lonely Jee-rasoni is left alone as always.)
I can't believe you caught that.
Of course I did.
(Quietly approaching)
- It's tasty. - Shall we take a photo?
- Just like that? - Take one for us.
(Holding on so he can't steal any meat)
Take our photo. One...
We haven't taken a photo in a while.
- Hair's getting in my mouth. - Let's pose.
- One, two... - One...
(A rock-solid defense)
- Two, three. - Two, three.
Darn it.
It came out nice.
He wanted to take a group photo...
(He leaves without nothing but memories instead of meat.)
That's madness. They saw through me.
(Time to interview the grand duke)
- Grand Duke of the Belly. - Yes.
What do you think about the state of your nation?
The state of my nation? It's...
There's a loach that's muddying the waters.
I must drive him out of my nation immediately.
He must get spat on the face.
He must be utterly humiliated so he's reminded of his place.
(He can hear everything.)
I took him in because I thought he'd end up in a ditch somewhere.
That beggar...
He must be thrown out pantless...
and left to get soaked by the rain.
Hey, if you think about it,
Seok Jin did nothing wrong.
(Jee Seok Jin, the whistling beggar)
- What did I do wrong? - What did he do?
Who do you think is the outsider?
I don't think the outsider is among us.
But Seok Jin wanted to take a group photo earlier.
He's not the type to want to take photos.
(His sudden behavior is highly suspicious.)
If that's a hidden mission, Seok Jin's a strong possibility.
(While suspicion is growing within Team North,)
Then...
- Breakfast... - It's here.
(Team North's food is served.)
- The bread... - Thank you.
We get all this?
- Thanks for the food. - I like this. Outback bread.
(Excited)
- Yes. - Outback Steakhouse.
(Only a piece of bread can make Food Fighter happy.)
- Ye Eun. - Yes?
- You don't dislike any food. - Come on...
Outback Steakhouse's bread...
It's so tasty.
(Savoring)
(Applause)
This is enough for me. How can bread be so...
(Everyone is enjoying it.)
You baked them so well.
(The flying fish roe pasta is served.)
- It's so pretty. - It looks amazing.
- Grand Duke, take some first. - Okay.
- Serve yourself first. - Serve yourself.
(The youngest one is not used to the class system.)
There's a strict hierarchy.
Gosh, it's good.
- The pasta... - The bread is so good.
(Twirling)
It's delicious.
(He gives it to Jae Seok first.)
- Serve yourself first. - Why...
- You... - Grand Duke.
(Thank you.)
Grand Duke.
- This is too little. - That's too little.
You gave me so little.
(A small serving to show his big heart)
It tastes good.
He fills another plate.
(He puts more pasta on another plate.)
You can have that. You eat that.
(Delivered to Ji Eun)
- I can take my time. - What's going on?
(It wasn't for me?)
- You... - You have this.
You served another nation's beggar first?
(Laughing)
- I... - You can eat this.
Are you okay?
I'm going in order of age.
- You seem to be shocked. - Yes.
I thought he was going to serve me next.
You eat this.
- No, I... - No, go ahead.
- That's so funny. - You eat it.
- Can I have a little more? - Ye Eun.
(The point)
- Give me a little more. - Say that on a blind date?
- It's really annoying. - I thought it was mine.
(The fallen grand duchess can't resist her appetite.)
You blurted it out.
Some fish roe too, please.
(Adding fish roe)
And some veg.
Aren't you on a diet?
No, I can eat today. Thank you.
(Cheat day)
(The most generous portion)
You ordered a steak earlier.
- You can eat the rest. - Yes.
- Grand Duke. Eat. - Eat the rest.
(The grand duke eats after serving his people.)
It's tasty.
It's so good.
(Eating)
- It's delicious. - It's fresh.
Why did you give the beggar so much food?
- She got a lot. - Why...
I was getting food for her,
and I kept hearing a hallucination from my right.
- "I want more." - Give me a little more.
- She said that? - "Some fish roe too."
(A hallucination with very specific demands)
- Some fish roe too, please. - "And some veg."
- And some veg. - It looks like...
she enjoys eating.
She has a hearty appetite.
(Everyone filled their stomachs.)
Ji Eun eats so well.
She was really hungry.
What could this be? How fun will this game be?
(The two families have returned from their meal out.)
- What's this? - Isn't it that game?
- What I did before. - What you did.
- Oh... - Oh, dear. This looks...
(The physical game set looks familiar somehow.)
- No way. - Seok Jin fell backward.
Wasn't he dressed like this that time too?
I was a beggar then too.
(Right)
- Good luck. - Good luck.
(The Joseon gambler episode from summer 3 years ago)
(Seok Sam hit himself in the back of the head.)
It is that same game.
I was actually scared that time.
(Seok Sam's worried already.)
- It's fine if you're clueless. - This game...
That's true.
(Ji Eun enters.)
That was so funny.
You changed clothes. The funny makeup is gone too.
That is what's happening.
- That's it. - You didn't take it off.
(Ji Eun removed her beggar makeup, following the instructions.)
You can't fall on purpose.
- You look different. - Weren't we supposed to clean up?
- You're a guest. - We kept it on.
(They heard it too, but they were too lazy to remove their makeup.)
- Sit down. - Come here, beggar.
- Beggar. - Take a seat.
Weren't we supposed to clean up?
Ji Eun looks like that actor from "Coffee Prince."
- What? - Yoon Eun Hye.
She does look a bit like her.
Why was I told to take off the beggar makeup?
(The final mission is revealed.)
The last mission is called Fly, Grand Duke, Fly.
You're playing to save your nation and win a hint about the outsiders.
(1. Absorb the opposing kingdom. 2. Gain a hint about the outsider.)
- We need a hint. - We do.
- One person per team will compete. - Okay.
You must squat low, holding a bowl full of water.
You'll hop onto four tiles to reach the other end of the mat...
and pour whatever water is in your bowl into the bucket.
Once you're done, you can run back to the start.
The team that collects the most water...
- in 100 seconds wins. - Gosh.
Collected in that bucket?
How do you hop onto those?
I have a fear of this game.
- This game traumatized me. - I'd love to see this work.
Pick someone to represent your team.
(They'll pick the players for Round 1.)
Seok Jin will represent us.
(Seok Sam, who's played this game, will go first.)
- This game requires a mouth guard. - Right.
- You can bite your tongue. - Totally.
Okay.
(Jae Seok on Team North is his opponent.)
- Oh, dear. - Let's go.
Shall I draw a line of snot?
- Yes. - Would that be better?
(Ji Eun's getting her face retouched voluntarily.)
Isn't this enough?
Take a look.
One person from each team...
(Ji Eun and Ji Hyo will help them.)
- will hop along. - Use your core muscles.
Your core muscles.
Okay. Ready?
- He'll do well, I think. - Go.
(Start)
(Yelping)
- He'll do well, I think. - Good luck.
(He spilled half the water already.)
It's fine. It's okay.
Jump.
Oh, dear.
(Seok Sam almost spilled everything.)
Seok Jin! Why did you drop that?
The memory from three years ago...
(Trauma)
- I can't help it. - Don't drop the bag.
(Refill)
Here goes.
- All right! - Good luck!
(The grasshopper's hopping well?)
- Here goes. - Good luck!
(He fails.)
Oh, dear.
Hurry.
He went down.
- He got scared. - Totally.
Hop gently like a rabbit.
It's so slippery.
(It seems Jae Seok got the hang of it.)
It's harder because the tiles are spaced out.
- Use your core muscles. - My core muscles.
- You can do it. - That's it.
You can do it.
(Safe)
Oh, dear.
(Gasping)
(Falling backward)
- He's funny. - He scored.
(Entertaining his fans)
- This game... - Seok Jin's...
(The Seok Sam Show is on.)
- It's Seok Sam's game. - You're the master.
(The expert took a hilarious tumble.)
It's Seok Sam's game.
- You're the master. - Did you see that?
This is slapstick.
You're so good at this.
(But he spilled everything.)
I'm not good at it. I just can't help myself.
- Look. Like there are stairs. - Darn it.
(The final course)
It's okay to spill some.
(Even Jae Seok fell.)
That's it!
You can do it.
(Jae Seok still has some water left.)
(Team North)
- Watch my core. - Go forward.
Go. Go ahead.
(While Jae Seok is refilling the pouch,)
(Seok Sam didn't reach the end yet.)
- Strengthen my core. - Go.
- That was a good jump. - He's at it again.
- Jump. - You must jump over that.
(The last hurdle)
He got scared.
- Good. - You need to stay squatting.
(Pouring)
- Hurry back. - He had a lot left.
(Keeping him in check)
That's still a lot. Help me out here.
(Team Belly)
It's not easy!
It's not easy.
- It feels a bit like... - It's not a game if it's easy.
You have 30 seconds to go.
(30 seconds are left!)
- Thirty seconds to go. - There's not much time left!
Okay!
- You can do it! - Good luck.
(All the water's gone!)
(Seok Sam's chance to get ahead!)
Nice one!
- Oh, no. - He's scared.
Don't be scared!
Don't be scared! Let's go!
(Hypnotizing himself)
- He's scared. - He got scared.
I have a trauma about this game.
Ten seconds to go.
(10 seconds are left!)
- It'll be close. - Come on.
- Go, Seok Sam. - Our team...
Are you swimming?
No!
(Just then)
- No! - Hurry. Go ahead.
(Jae Seok fell again. It's Seok Sam's chance!)
- No! - Yes.
- Oh, no. - The water...
(Grunting)
- Seok Jin! - Yes.
- Oh, no. - Seok Jin!
(He fell into a ditch.)
- Two, one. - Get up!
(The time is up.)
He fell into the ditch.
What happened?
(The master finishes it off with some perfect slapstick.)
- Gosh. - That was...
- I thought you fainted. - I think they won.
I fell into the ditch.
- Ji Eun. - Ji Eun will go next.
(Beggar Ji Eun will play this time.)
- Me? - Will you have a go?
Okay.
Shall I support her?
(SAN will support her.)
Yes, you do that.
How do I do this?
- Shall I support her? - Yes, you do that.
Shoot. This is scary.
(Ji Eun is warming up awkwardly.)
- It doesn't hurt at all. - She must have a strong core.
- I'm worried about my back. - You won't fall like that.
(Haha on Team Belly will play.)
It has nothing to do with core muscles.
Does my wig look weird?
- Is it the right way? - No.
(He's serious about his beggar look.)
It's wrong?
- It's crooked. - Right?
- I'll ace this. - Ready.
(Round 2 begins.)
- Do well. - I'll do really well.
You can do this.
(Gasping)
(Laughing)
What just happened?
(Did he lose his memory?)
Get back here already!
- That happens. - There's no water left!
You can do it.
(Slipping and falling)
- Ji Eun. - You can do this.
(Yelping)
- Gosh. - Ji Eun.
Well done, Ji Eun. You're doing great.
- You're doing well. - You're fine.
(Haha's 2nd attempt)
- Ji Eun. - You're okay.
One person...
- I jump from here? - Don't be scared.
- Yes. - From there to here.
Hey, Haha.
(Slide, thud)
What just happened?
(Right up his alley)
- "What just happened?" - What happened?
What happened?
(Goldfish Ha lost his memory.)
(While this actress wants to get into slapstick.)
- She's struggling too. - Are you okay, Ji Eun?
- Ji Eun. - It's okay.
(The former grand duchess became a mess.)
Haha is off.
(Anticipating)
You look like the heroine from a tragedy.
(Haha enters the final course.)
- Haha is on fire today. - I don't know what to do.
That part is fine, Haha.
That's it.
(Pouring)
- Okay. That's it. - Come on, Ji Eun.
- Ji Eun. - My goodness.
(Ji Eun managed to reach the end.)
Ji Eun is working hard.
- Ji Eun. - Didn't you bite your tongue?
Nice.
- You can pour in the water now. - Nice.
(Kind)
- Seriously, Ji Eun. - Okay.
(Each of them did it once!)
- That's it, Haha. Good job. - Let's go.
It's too far.
It's okay.
That's it.
- Come back. - No, there is some water left.
Go.
(Encouraged by their teammates, they move forward.)
There you go.
- You're at the end. - Come on.
(Groaning)
- You can pour in the water now. - I'm exhausted.
- Thirty seconds remain. - Haha!
(30 seconds are left!)
Haha, do it one more time.
- There is a lot of water. - You can do it.
- Do it 1 more time. - Ji Eun, do it 1 more time.
(They can do it one more time!)
- You don't have much time. - Ji Eun.
- Are you okay? - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
- Mister! - I'm sorry.
Darn it!
(Haha's team's bucket)
Gosh, I'm sorry.
(He spills it!)
- Mister! - I'm sorry.
- For goodness' sake. - Are you kidding me?
- Mister! - That's just wrong!
(He makes a big mistake while trying to walk past by.)
- Mister! - I'm sorry. Seriously.
- That's just wrong. - What are you doing?
- I mean... - This is ridiculous.
- I slipped on my way. - Oh, no.
- I mean... - I can't believe you.
You're the worst!
- Oh, no. - I slipped.
- I slipped. - I can't believe you.
(Angry)
- We had so much water. - I slipped.
- It was a mistake. - What are you going to do about it?
Jae Seok, don't make any more mistakes.
- I won't. - "Any more mistakes?"
(Flustered)
- Hey! - Hey!
- Are you kidding me? - What kind of a director...
Hey, Saemaeul-ho!
(Producer Ma Ro)
- I'm sorry. - No more mistakes.
(He's adding fuel to the fire.)
- I'm sorry. - I mean...
- I'm sorry. - You call that a mistake?
- It was a mistake. - I can't believe it.
- It wasn't a mistake. - I slipped.
(They'll finish the game first!)
Ten seconds remain.
(The last 10 seconds)
Ten seconds remain, Haha.
(Sliding at the same time)
Are you okay?
All right! I saved some water.
- Five seconds. - All right.
- Five seconds. One last time. - Go a bit further.
- Five, four, - Haha.
(Haha is almost there.)
- One last time. Haha. - three,
- Go. Come on. - two...
- Go. Come on. - Two...
Pour it in there.
(Oh, no)
- No! - Hey!
Oh, no!
Hey!
(Haha spills the water.)
Hey.
You spilled all the water.
(Ji Eun also poured the water for the last time.)
- Why did you spill it? - You spilled all of it.
Hey, hurry up and scoop up the water on the floor.
(He quickly adds more water by hand.)
- You still have a chance. - Haha, what was that?
There is more water than I expected.
(Viper eyes)
Blame the person who tipped over our bucket!
- It was a mistake. - We had so much water.
(They will take into account the water Jae Seok spilled.)
- They'll take that into account. - The amount was similar.
(Team North, Team Belly)
Ji Ye Eun, come on out.
(Ji Hyo from Team Belly versus Ye Eun from Team North)
- Ye Eun. - Yes?
Victory is ours.
Victory is...
- ours! - Ours!
- Get ready. - Good luck.
Set.
(Start)
- No, Ye Eun... - My goodness.
(Groaning)
(The titan falls.)
(Grunting)
- Ye Eun. - What are you doing?
- She is like a paper doll. - That's funny.
Ye Eun, go.
(The paper doll gets wet.)
Come on, you punk!
- Oh, my. - Ye Eun, that's good.
- My goodness. - It's okay.
(Ji Hyo also falls.)
My goodness.
But Ji Hyo saves the water.
- What are you doing? - Okay.
(She didn't spill much.)
- That's it. - You're good.
You're good. You saved a lot of water.
(Ji Hyo gets the hang of it.)
- It looks like Ji Hyo will win. - No.
(It's quite a lot of water.)
- Really? - Hurry up. Do it one more time.
Ji Hyo, hurry up. You're doing better than her.
Ten,
(The Game Queen keeps the water like an expert.)
- That's good. - nine...
- You need to keep going. - You saved a lot of water.
- Nice. - Go over the line.
(It's the last chance for both.)
- Nice. - Five,
- four, - That's incredible.
(Pouring)
- three... - That's a lot of water.
(Trickling)
- Okay. - Three,
- two, one. - All right.
(Team North, Team Belly)
(Thanks to Ji Hyo, they now have a similar amount of water.)
Hey, Ji Hyo won.
- We're neck and neck. - The amount is similar.
That's right. We're neck and neck.
Okay, Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook is the last player from Team Belly.)
Okay. Let's do this.
- SAN. - SAN will go next.
(SAN is the last player from Team North.)
Maybe we have less water.
- Are we winning? - Come on.
We can do it.
Nice.
(The fate of the two kingdoms rests on the final round.)
- Good luck. - Let's go.
Let's turn the tables.
- All right. Get ready. - Good luck.
Set.
(Start)
That's good.
(Both of them charge forward.)
- Come on. - They slid forward.
(At that moment)
(SAN holds his position with his strong core.)
He doesn't disappoint.
(He reaches the finish line in no time.)
(When SAN scores for the first time)
Jong Kook, hurry up and pick up the pace.
(Falling)
(Shouting)
What's wrong with him?
Pick up the pace.
(Please)
Jong Kook has met his match.
(Grunting)
Right now, SAN...
How far will it move?
Jong Kook, hurry up.
(Waddling along, Jong Kook poured the water for the first time.)
You can do it.
Here I go.
(Meanwhile, SAN charges forward once more.)
- SAN, that's good. - That's it.
(Impressed)
- SAN is twice as fast. - That's good.
SAN, that's good.
- Nice. Nice, SAN. - That's good.
Nice.
Nice, San.
(He wraps up in a cool way!)
It's okay. I got this.
What's this?
(Falling)
Ji Eun, is it your turn?
- Ji Eun, is it your turn? - No.
(Regardless, SAN keeps moving along.)
Jong Kook, you're behind by one lap.
- Hurry up. - It's too far.
(Tripping)
(His heavy body goes down with a thud.)
Go!
- Just go! - That's good.
- That's good. - Don't get intimidated.
(Staggering)
- Don't get intimidated. - SAN, that's good.
- That's good. - He is young.
(Desperately doing his best)
- Jong Kook, don't get intimidated. - That's funny.
(While Jong Kook plays with water)
- That's good. - He is young.
- He is young. - That's funny.
(SAN, a man who lives and dies by style is nearing the finish line.)
- That's it. - He is young.
That's funny.
- He is young. - He is young.
(Sliding again)
- Nice. - All right.
Nice. Good job.
How is he so good at it?
- He is like a game machine. - We'll win.
- SAN has... - He is so fast.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook refilled the water.)
- good techniques. - He...
- He might as well be a frog. - He is like a frog.
That's good.
(Tripping right away)
- Jong Kook! - That's good.
Jong Kook!
(Jong Kook can't seem to get the hang of it.)
- Nice. - You fell off the mat.
You fell off the mat.
Jong Kook isn't so athletic anymore.
(Heave-ho)
He is bad at this.
- How is he so bad it? - He is...
just an insistent middle-aged man.
- Ten seconds remain. - SAN is working hard.
(The last 10 seconds)
SAN is good.
Well done.
(Cheering)
(He wraps up with a relieved sigh!)
- One last time. - He is so fast.
(He nailed the final shot.)
- He is good. - Nice.
What happened to Jong Kook?
(Jong Kook doesn't have much time left.)
Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook can't stop falling down.)
- I mean... - Jong Kook became...
- a funny middle-aged man. - Oh, my.
He lost.
(He barely finished it.)
Jong Kook.
- He totally lost. - No.
How many trips did SAN make?
(The game is over.)
I think SAN made seven trips.
- It was insane. - He made so many trips.
- SAN made so many trips. - We won.
(Grunting)
It was insane.
(Cheering)
(They get addicted to the chest dance.)
Do the dance.
- Let's do it together. - My goodness.
It was incredible.
Nice.
(They already think they won.)
We won.
SAN was so fast.
(Panting)
- Well done, SAN. - He is young.
- He is young. - He is definitely young.
(Thank you.)
- He is different. - He is different indeed.
Jong Kook, why did you do so badly?
- I mean, - Jong Kook was good...
(All he did was make the others laugh.)
- at slapstick comedy. - my heavy body...
My heavy body made me slip.
You were like a bullfrog.
Seriously.
(So the winning team is...)
Here comes the result of the mission.
Team North's water is 21.5cm deep.
Team Belly's water is 15cm deep.
Team North won.
(Although Jae Seok spilled 4cm, Team North won!)
I mean...
Okay! Nice.
(It was a victory powered by SAN's impressive performance!)
We won.
It was incredible.
Nice.
- If he hadn't spilled the water... - I know.
(Team Belly lost a close game.)
If he hadn't done that...
He spilled our water.
Seriously,
Jae Seok will pay for this.
I know. He'll pay for this.
We would've won regardless.
(Teasing)
He has a point.
(Oh, gosh)
Now, Team Belly...
- will be disassembled. - Okay.
The members will join Team North.
(The Grand Duke of North's domain, The Grand Duke of Belly's domain)
(The Grand Duke of North finally united the three kingdoms.)
We'll be one team.
Are all of us in the same team now?
As you carried out the missions,
the outsiders completed...
the hidden mission behind your back.
- What? - Did they do something?
The outsiders completed the hidden mission behind your back.
(The outsiders completed the hidden mission.)
- What? - Did they do something?
- They completed it? - What did they do?
Did they do something?
- Did they do something? - What did they do?
Two outsiders completed the hidden mission,
- so you won't get more hints. - What?
What?
Although the hints have been locked,
(However)
the winning team can get the last hint for the mission.
The leader of the winning team, the Grand Duke of the North,
can get the last hint on the outsiders.
Please come and check it out.
(What's the last hint SAN will get?)
- None of us are outsiders. - Among us...
- None of us are outsiders. - SAN, check one...
- of the team members. - That's right.
Here comes the last hint.
If you pick one of your people whom you suspect to be...
an outsider,
we'll tell you if he or she is one.
Please write the name of your suspect on the card.
- Whom do you suspect? - Me?
Ji Eun.
Seok Jin too.
Does Team Fools have an outsider?
(SAN received the first hint in the morning.)
(Does Team Fools have an outsider?)
The outsiders...
- Yes. - Okay.
(One of them is an outsider.)
(Whose identity will SAN check?)
I'll check Ji Eun's identity.
I suspect her.
(Is Ji Eun an outsider?)
It's hard to be a spy.
What is it?
Here is the result.
(The result is revealed.)
The two of you are the outsiders who infiltrated the nation...
(Is Ji Eun an outsider who was given a mission beforehand?)
that's ruled by grand dukes.
- Here is the result. - Was I right?
(Ji Eun)
(Ji Eun is an outsider.)
I got it right.
I'll have to see.
I think things will go well today.
After all, the makeup artist who did my makeup said...
she had a dream about me.
(Outsider Ji Eun was full of confidence.)
She told me that it was a good sign.
(During the opening)
- Welcome. Let's see. - Welcome.
- What? Ji Eun is sweating. - Are we looking for spies?
My hands and feet get cold.
(Giving an absurd answer)
Really?
(She was suspected from the very start.)
Here it comes.
A tiger doesn't fear a tiger.
- What? - That's...
She is suspicious.
(Her ridiculous answer was a decisive hint.)
No!
- Ji Eun is too... - "A tiger..."
- She is a spy. - Is she a spy?
- Why... - It isn't like that.
(She made many mistakes.)
We need to win.
I got it right.
(She's caught in the end.)
- SAN, did you get the hint? - SAN.
I apprehended one outsider.
- Really? - Who is it?
- I got it right. - Who is it?
(Nervous)
Nice.
- You can tell us. - It's Ji Eun, right?
- That's right. - Can he tell us?
- You can tell us. - Tell us.
(Moving her eyes around)
But we still don't know who the other outsider is.
(Careful)
- Don't do anything. - That's right. Keep quiet.
- The grand dukes will discuss it. - Okay.
- That's right. - The grand dukes.
- Aren't the grand dukes poor now? - At this point...
It's Ji Eun.
- Right? I knew it. - Ji Ye Eun?
(2 outsiders)
- Ji Eun. - That much is certain.
- That's right. - But we don't have any hints...
(The rest...)
about the other one.
What could be the hidden mission they succeeded in?
- Earlier, Seok Jin... - Yes.
- asked for a group photo. - Yes.
Wasn't that strange?
How about a group photo?
- That's so sudden. - Please take a photo of us.
(Was the sudden family photo a hidden mission?)
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
- It was strange, but... - It was strange, right?
maybe it was a ploy...
- to eat meat. - Right. When you think about it,
(It could've been a trick to have meat.)
it wasn't completely unnecessary.
Would the production team put two outsiders on the same team?
- I don't think so. - More than Seok Jin,
- I suspect Jong Kook and Jae Seok. - Jong Kook.
- Same here. Jae Seok. - I think...
(It looks like everyone agrees.)
- Jong Kook has been acting strange. - That's right.
So it's either Jong Kook or Jae Seok.
Jong Kook is usually good at such games.
(Suspect 1, Bullfrog)
It was so strange.
Jae Seok knocked over the bucket too.
(Suspect 2, Prankster)
It was strange indeed.
He did the chest dance whenever he saw you.
He kept doing the dance.
(The top two members the Grand Dukes are suspecting)
- It's hard. - We won't get any more hints.
Let's ask for their opinions and study their reactions.
- Let's do that. - Listen.
- They might feign ignorance. - Let's ask Ji Eun...
this question.
"Do you think it's Jae Seok or Jong Kook?"
If she picks Jae Seok, it'll be Jong Kook. Right?
- I see. A leading question. - That's right.
(While the Grand Dukes are planning to sound them out...)
Please give us some names.
(The common people want to solve it together.)
- We can't tell you now. - Tell us who the outsider is...
- so that we can make deductions. - That's right.
- We'll need to talk to some people. - Okay.
(They're going to sound Ji Eun out just as they planned.)
- Overall... - What if we mess up?
Let's make deductions separately.
Ji Eun, who do you think is the outsider?
(Asking casually)
My first guess is...
- Seok Sam? - Seok Jin. Yes.
- I'm not an outsider. - Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin isn't it. - No.
(Since Ji Eun picked Seok Sam, he wouldn't be an outsider.)
- SAN, come here. - SAN.
- For goodness' sake. - Tell us.
I love this trio.
- Seok Jin isn't an outsider. - Me?
I don't think it's him.
- I thought... - Suddenly...
In the beginning?
- Seok Jin, tell us. - What?
What did I do?
- What are you doing? - I didn't do anything.
We're a team.
- I'm certain of it. - Okay.
Grasshopper and Ji Eun.
- For goodness' sake. - They're the outsiders.
(Seok Sam picks Jae Seok and Ji Eun.)
- I got goosebumps. - You're so clueless.
Grasshopper did act strange.
For goodness' sake.
You're so clueless.
- Grasshopper did act strange. - I agree with him.
- You're so clueless. - Jae Seok might be right.
- Grasshopper and... - The dance was suspicious.
(It must be a hidden mission.)
Jae Seok.
I suspect Ji Eun...
(What does Jae Seok think?)
and Jong Kook.
- Why Jong Kook so suddenly? - Why?
Bullfrog?
Jong Kook's bullfrog impression during the last game was too much.
(It's suspicious that he played the game too poorly.)
- He could've done better. - Yes.
- He usually does better than that. - I agree.
(He's actually a little better at games.)
- That's right. - I focused on being funny...
(I was only trying to make it fun. I didn't lose on purpose.)
instead of doing well.
- I thought it was funny. - Right.
You laughed a lot.
- He has a point. - Right.
- Okay. - Jong Kook, how about you?
I can't help but think this way,
judging by the flow of things.
- You can't help it? - Ji Eun.
- Ji Eun. - Ji Eun.
- Ji Eun is an outsider. - She is definitely one of them.
To be honest, I've been suspicious of Seok Jin.
That's right. It's either Seok Jin or you.
I'm not it.
Why me?
- Maybe it's Jae Seok. - I'm not an outsider, okay?
(Jong Kook is suspicious of Jae Seok too.)
Gosh, I'm so frustrated. I'm not an outsider.
I'm not an outsider, okay?
I'm sorry, but why did you kick the bucket earlier?
- Seriously. - Why...
(The slapstick comedy using the bucket is hard to understand.)
- Was it a mission? - I...
Were you being mischievous or...
- While I'm mischievous... - Listen.
You could've spilled a little bit of water.
- But you just knocked it over. - Couldn't you hold it in?
- Couldn't you hold it in? - I couldn't hold it in.
- Why couldn't you hold it in? - I'm so sorry.
(Jae Seok was only being playful out of habit?)
- I apologize once more. - It wasn't like...
we were winning by a landslide.
(Grumbling)
We were just a little bit ahead.
Please think of it as an occupational habit.
An occupational habit?
His explanation was very logical.
Also, you complained a lot when you saw us do this dance...
- during the opening. - Right.
- But... - Then you began doing the dance.
Why did you do that?
Was it a mission?
(Twitching)
Why did you do that? Were you scared?
(Bad visuals)
I like the dance.
(That's because I like it.)
Then please look at the Jimmy Jib and do the dance.
Do what?
Did someone trample on you?
Are you hiccuping?
- Does something smell bad? - Are you hiccuping?
(He turns it into the hiccuping dance.)
Does something smell bad?
- Seriously. - He is so polite.
(Polite)
- Well done. - I'm very polite.
(Is the chest dance addicted member not an outsider?)
I apologize for what I did earlier.
I'm not an outsider. Please believe me.
Isn't Seok Jin being too quiet?
No. Seok Jin.
(Shaking)
- Why are you being too quiet? - I'm sorry, but...
- stop pretending to be a spy. - Stop it.
- Seriously. - We know you aren't a spy.
(Seok Sam who is quiet is suspicious too.)
- You're confusing us further. - I haven't done anything.
It's time for the final vote.
If you successfully exile the two outsiders,
(Place of exile)
the outsiders will receive the penalty.
(Penalty)
If you only exile one outsider or fail to exile either one of them,
the outsiders will win, and the three grand dukes...
and one member of their choice will get the penalty.
(Penalty)
Okay.
Now, if you aren't...
(Ji Eun is confirmed as an outsider.)
the grand duke, please vote for Ji Eun.
(They just need to find one more.)
- We'll... - Vote for one person.
- We'll do that. - Okay.
- That way, we won't fight. - That's a good idea.
What?
- I'm the Outsider Dance. - I knew she was acting strange.
- She wasn't in her right mind. - When I high-fived her...
during the opening, her hand was like a water bomb.
It's Ji Eun.
(Feigning innocence until the very end)
I'm not an outsider.
Han Ji Eun and the grand dukes' choice...
- We'll be discreet. - Okay.
- SAN will tell you. - SAN.
They keep acting like they're on the same team as SAN.
I know. SAN is a member of our team.
(Show-offs who strut around with SAN at their side)
- They're such an eyesore. - This is ridiculous.
- I can't believe them. - Seriously.
- Who do they think they are? - You know,
- they have vastly different looks. - Seriously.
Jong Kook.
- I can't believe them. - Seriously.
(The grand dukes with varying looks choose Jong Kook.)
- Who do they think they are? - You know...
What do you think?
- We're done. - This is ridiculous.
(Is Jong Kook an outsider?)
- We made it fun. - Okay.
I don't know. You guys are so hard to figure out.
It's so hard.
- If you hear your name, - Shall we step forward?
(The outsider candidates chosen are sent to an exile place.)
- that means you're exiled. - Who are the outsiders?
(Exile place)
- Okay. - They'll be exiled.
- Han Ji Eun, you're exiled. - That's right.
(First outsider, Ji Eun)
I'm not it.
You fools.
Fine, I'm an outsider.
Maybe she isn't an outsider.
(Easily swayed)
- It's her. - I mean...
The member the grand dukes chose as an outsider is...
Jong Kook?
- Kim Jong Kook. You're exiled. - Jong Kook.
(Second outsider, Jong Kook)
Really? Are we wrong?
- This is driving me crazy. - Isn't it Jong Kook?
For goodness' sake.
(Glaring)
- Isn't it Jong Kook? - It's Seok Jin.
- Seriously. - SAN...
- SAN picked you. - There wasn't any evidence...
- against me. Why me? - Isn't it Jae Seok?
We were torn between Jong Kook and Jae Seok.
So why did you pick me?
(Interrogating)
- What was the reason? - The reason.
- Bullfrog? - Bullfrog.
The bullfrog impression played a big role.
(Bullfrog became a key clue.)
- Because of that... - I'll be boring from now on.
I swear I'll be boring.
(The poisonous frog throws a fit.)
This is driving me crazy.
I'll be boring from now on.
(Watching carefully)
- I guess it isn't Jong Kook! - I swear I'll be boring.
(The grand dukes are confused as he's really throwing a fit.)
- I guess it isn't him! - This is driving me crazy.
Is it Jae Seok?
- I mean... - No!
It isn't me!
- There was... - Toward the end,
- you framed Jae Seok... - That's right.
- excessively. We went, "What?" - That's right.
- "Jong Kook isn't like that." - I'm not it.
Was it because of the game?
It wasn't because of the game. You were too...
- You framed Jae Seok. - That's right.
- I framed Jae Seok? - Yes.
I framed Jae Seok?
I can't believe you guys.
(Upset)
You made a groundless accusation.
It's either Jong Kook or Seok Jin.
Is it Seok Jin?
Seok Jin did take a group photo.
(Investigation back to square one)
That's right. I think it's Seok Sam.
- I'm not an outsider. - If it really is him...
(Remaining calm)
Please don't be like that.
What have I done?
- Stop swaying us. - I haven't done anything.
- I think it's Seok Sam. - I stayed still.
Let's just check the result.
Wait. "Let's just check the result?"
- I'm not it. - "Let's just check the result."
- SAN. What should we do? - SAN, wait.
- Shall we go with this choice? - Judging by Jong Kook's face,
(Reconvening the meeting among grand dukes)
- he isn't it. - I don't think it's him.
- I don't think it's him. - Look at his facial expression.
Hey, I'm serious. Don't do something you'll regret.
(Turning serious)
- I don't think it's Jong Kook. - It isn't Jong Kook.
- Let's go with Jae Seok. - Jong Kook, come on down.
- Let's go with Jae Seok. - Jae Seok,
- you're too suspicious. - It isn't me.
(The grand dukes change their choice.)
- Jae Seok, go up there. - For goodness' sake.
Go up there.
(Sending Jae Seok to the place of exile instead of Jong Kook)
I didn't want to push my opinion before.
- It really isn't me. - I'm certain it's Jae Seok.
- Go up there. - It really isn't me.
- Go up there. - He wanted us to hurry up.
Let's just check the result.
(Jae Seok was going to rush and turn Jong Kook in.)
- Why did you want us to hurry up? - Go up there.
- It's Jae Seok. - Seriously.
SAN, say it once more.
I think it's Jae Seok!
SAN, it isn't me.
- Jae Seok, you're exiled. - It isn't...
- It isn't me! - No?
- It isn't me! This is insane. - No?
(Is Jae Seok doing the "Bad" dance because he is an outsider?)
- Jong Kook's reaction convinced me. - I mean...
- It's Jong Kook or Seok Jin. - It can't be Jong Kook.
- It really isn't me. - It can't be Jong Kook.
(Suspecting his expression)
- It isn't me. - It isn't me.
- He wants to wrap this up quickly. - It's Seok Jin.
- It's him. - Just go up there.
(Certain)
Go up there, Jae Seok.
Yang Se Chan, that little...
- Jae Seok and Ji Eun. - You utter fool!
(Final decision, Ji Eun and Jae Seok)
If one of them isn't an outsider,
- you'll get a smoke. - Seriously.
- If they're outsiders, - You're it.
- you won't get smoke. - No.
(If Jae Seok is an outsider, the grand dukes will win.)
- All right. - Isn't it Jae Seok?
We'll announce the result.
Please.
- Please. - All right. One.
(They changed their choice at the very end.)
(Is Jae Seok an outsider?)
Two.
Three.
(They failed to apprehend the outsiders.)
(Jae Seok wasn't an outsider.)
- What? - I'm not it.
- It's him! - It's Seok Jin.
- What? - Don't do it like that, Seok Jin!
Seriously!
(Is Seok Jin an outsider?)
- What's wrong with you? - It was Seok Jin.
Those two... Did we get it right or wrong?
Stop it already.
The carbon dioxide...
(He doesn't know the rule?)
I'm sick of this.
- What's wrong with you? - Don't do that!
- They... - We got it wrong!
The carbon dioxide exploded. Didn't we win?
- Seriously, he... - You...
(Is he faking it until the end by pretending not to know the rules?)
Is it you?
- No. - It's you.
It's not me!
The real outsider, please hold up your hand at the count of three.
- It's Jong Kook. - Seriously.
(There's a big confusion. Who is the real outsider?)
- One, two, - I told you it wasn't me.
- three! - Who is it?
(Is it Jong Kook who escaped the dragnet at the end?)
- It's Jong Kook! - Two...
- Is it Ji Hyo? - It's Jong Kook!
(Is it Seok Sam who is acting like a fool until the end?)
It's him.
- Who is it? - Please hold up your hand.
(Confused)
Do I hold up my hand?
(Embarrassed)
Hey!
- Do I hold up my hand? - Hey!
(Jong Kook was the outsider.)
- It was him! - Seriously.
(Feeling betrayed)
Do I hold up my hand?
It was him!
I shouldn't have changed my mind!
What a relief.
(Thanks to Jong Kook pulling off a serious look,)
Right from the start, she...
(the outsiders could keep their identities hidden.)
The two of you are outsiders.
(Outsider Ji Eun...)
(and another outsider, Jong Kook)
- Me? - Yes.
Actually, I don't want to do this.
(Jong Kook played the role of a spy after a long time.)
Being a spy really kills you.
(Pressured)
- I'm... - It's nerve-racking.
We know each other so well now.
I might get caught in the middle.
But you have a powerful weapon. Your incredible strength.
- Let's do it well. - Okay.
- You have a hidden mission. - Yes.
(A hidden mission given to the outsiders)
- There will be three teams. - Yes.
If you end up on the same team when the teams merge,
(When 3 teams merge to form 2 teams,)
(they must be in different teams.)
you fail the hidden mission, and the hint about the outsiders...
(If they fail, a hint about outsiders will be revealed.)
will be revealed.
- I see. - If you feel like...
- you'll get caught, - Yes.
just abandon me.
Okay.
(The so-called "cutting ties" operation)
- Yes. We could suspect each other. - Yes.
You're trying to lose on purpose, aren't you?
- Why would I try to lose? - The Grand Duke of the Belly...
It's not me. There's no outsider among us.
(Jong Kook tried to frame a member...)
- The grand dukes are excluded. - It's not among us.
(as Detective Kook and almost got himself suspected.)
Okay. Let's proceed.
(Feeling nervous)
Don't you think it's Jong Kook?
It's possible.
(Ji Eun tried to abandon him by casting suspicion on Jong Kook.)
Actually, for us,
- it's safest to just bring Haha. - That's a safe choice.
(When the three teams merged,)
(which was the outsiders' hidden mission)
- We're suspicious of Ji Eun. - Ji Eun...
It's 100 percent her.
- Ji Eun... - I think it's her.
(Going along)
Ji Eun.
Ji Eun's tiger thing was suspicious.
(As a result, the outsiders were split into different teams.)
- Tiger and tiger. - Yes. We'll take Seok Jin as well.
(They succeeded in the hidden mission by cutting their ties.)
Seok Jin and I will be joining.
What a relief.
(It's a perfect victory for the outsiders,)
Right from the start, she...
(who avoided getting caught until the very end.)
I told you it was him. I said it was Jong Kook.
- Jae Seok. - This...
(Jae Seok was falsely accused.)
- He got really mad. - But Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook! - Wait. Did you have...
- to get so serious? - You really got mad.
- He just argued with it. - When did I get mad?
(The bullfrog avoided suspicion by pulling a serious face.)
It was him. I told you it was the bullfrog.
No! That's what I just did.
That's how I did it.
(What he really couldn't do)
Are you going to get so serious about it? Okay, fine.
In that case, I'll just... Okay.
The bullfrog was me just doing my best.
- What was it with him? - Why did you do that?
He just knocked down the container?
(He can't understand it.)
Why did you do this when you told us not to do it?
That's who I am.
- Why did you kick the container? - Why did you do this?
I'm just someone who does that.
(Prankster Yu dug his own grave because he couldn't hold back...)
- Why did you kick the container? - That's who I am.
(being a prankster.)
- He can't hold back. - I can't hold back.
(The behind story of Ddochi's wedding announcement...)
It's so hard.
(will be revealed soon.)
The outsiders were Jong Kook and Ji Eun.
The outsiders won at the end.
You'll get the gift certificates worth 300 dollars...
that the grand dukes have.
- Here you go. - How much is this?
(The grand dukes return the gift certificates.)
- It's 200 dollars. - It's 200 dollars.
Thank you.
The grand dukes and the people failed to capture the outsiders.
The three grand dukes and one person they pick...
will get the penalty.
Please pick one person you'll get the penalty with.
Let's have a discussion.
- You should... - Why bother choosing?
The playful child should come.
The playful child? This happened...
- because you chose me at the end. - What?
- Are you shouting at us? - Are you shouting at us?
No, Seok Sam should...
(Intimidated)
Jae Seok.
(Forget it.)
- We choose Jae Seok. - Get ready.
(Getting the penalty with Prankster Yu...)
- These guys... - It was good for me, but...
(who hampered the investigation)
- Today's penalty... - Seok Jin...
is getting flogged, which will help...
improve blood circulation in the lower body.
Okay!
We're wet right now.
Wet flogging!
(Perfect penalty for wet buttocks)
That will hurt a lot.
- Make it fun. - Look the other way.
- Look the other way. - Are you all right?
(How satisfying!)
(Lastly, it's the Grand Duke of the North's turn.)
- Seok Sam should hit him. - Yes.
All the bad luck...
(Laughing)
Why should I hit him?
- I mean... - You look like an executioner.
(Executioner Jee is scared of the backlash.)
- You look like an executioner. - Seok Jin.
- We all... - You look like an executioner.
He's a global star.
- Feel free to flog me. - That's right.
(Gentle)
That would make it fun.
Will your fans be okay with this?
- Of course. - Of course.
SAN is also...
Could you count to three before you hit me?
(Rushed)
Okay.
- One, - I'm sorry, fans.
- two... - Take it easy.
Wishing you huge success!
SAN!
- It would be hot. - SAN...
(Thank you to SAN, the Grand Duke of the North,)
(and Princess Ji Eun, who even conquered Running Man.)
Hey.
Thank you, Seok Jin.
(And at the next shoot)
What is this? You put a lot of effort...
(The members gathered upon Ye Eun's sudden announcement.)
for Ye Eun.
Goodness. They're trying to make use of it.
Shouldn't Vata be here at this point?
- Right. It's time. - He'll come out from here.
- Will he come? - Vata, please wait a bit.
(Even the groom-to-be is ready.)
It's pink.
- It's full of love. - My fingers are already...
Congratulations, Ye Eun!
(The reason the green room is decorated in a lovely way.)
- Congratulations, Ye Eun! - Come in quickly!
("Ye Eun and Vata to Marry on December 12")
- Today's star. - I knew about it.
I read it in the news.
("They Are Going to Build Their Lives Together")
- I knew it as well. - I also knew about it.
I'm jealous, Ye Eun!
- Say that to Ye Eun. - I'm jealous!
(Pouring out her true feelings to thin air)
Say it to Ye Eun.
She's jealous.
Since you said that, the atmosphere...
- Shall we sit down? - It's getting heavy.
- Why... - The cake looks pretty.
(They even prepared a cake to celebrate it.)
Isn't she the first married woman on Running Man?
- Really? - Yes. She's the first...
(It's a first to have a female member who's married.)
- married woman. - That's true.
- There are many married men. - There are many married men.
Since it's her first wedding, just put one candle.
(And a candle to celebrate her joining the married club)
Do you put two candles...
- for your second one? - Of course.
(That moment)
Ddochi!
(The party's star is here.)
- Congratulations on your wedding - Congratulations on your wedding
- Congratulations on your wedding - Thank you.
(Ddochi Ji, the bride-to-be)
- Thank you. - Congratulations,
(Congratulations, the first married woman of Running Man.)
- Ye Eun. - Ye Eun.
- Congratulations on your wedding - Congratulations on your wedding
- Thank you. - One, two, three.
- Congratulations! - Congratulations!
It's great news.
You're a married woman!
During last week's filming,
Ye Eun told us about it a little.
(Ye Eun shared the news to the members.)
- It... - She even mentioned the date.
- But we just moved on. - That's right.
- We didn't believe her. - They thought I was joking.
We filmed at a wedding hall, and Jae Seok told her,
- He told me to practice. - "Shouldn't you practice?"
A rehearsal.
- Shouldn't Ye Eun... - The bride's entrance.
(The bride's entrance)
- practice walking down the stairs? - Right. He said that.
So I said, "Should I practice that?"
Then Se Chan said, "Ji Hyo is going to believe this."
(What Se Chan said)
I thought, "He really thinks I'm joking."
(Se Chan thought she was joking.)
- You hope it's not true, right? - No.
- Goodness. - You sure?
- You hope it's not true. - Se Chan...
(It's his last time to make such jokes.)
- She's a bride-to-be. - She's a bride-to-be.
(Ye Eun became a bride-to-be.)
A bride-to-be.
(Embarrassed)
- Congratulations. - I envy you.
You should have gone first. I'm getting married first...
- Right. Why... - It's how everyone...
I have to respect my elders.
- Goodness. - By the way, Ye Eun...
revealed her relationship...
- with Vata. - Yes.
- That happened early this year. - Right.
It was around April or May. That's when I announced it.
(Their dating news broke in April.)
- That's right. - Right.
So you revealed your relationship...
- after deciding to get married. - That's right.
- You did that well. - People keep saying it's too early.
(People around her)
- They think I'm pregnant. - No.
The thing is, I don't have a child.
I don't have a child.
(Ji Ye Eun, "I'm not pregnant before the wedding.")
- That's right. - It's true.
- Of course. - That's not the case.
I can say this for sure. It's not true.
(Father Jee can speak for her.)
I'm not pregnant, and I don't have any plans yet.
I want to enjoy...
- my newlywed life for a while. - Yes.
(They're going to take their time to plan about having children.)
I want to enjoy my newlywed life.
- Of course. - What made you decide?
(The reason she decided to marry him)
- Right. - It's because...
he's such a warm person.
Even when we fight, he uses kind words.
- That's the most important part. - That's important.
It's important how you fight.
(He agrees as a married man.)
Even when I was sick, he was a great support.
- During that time. - I felt safe.
- That was the decisive moment. - Yes.
- When you were sick. - I think someone...
who stays by your side when you're sick is the best.
- That's right. - My father said...
he hid his personality for about three years.
(Killing the mood)
- Three years? - Why are you ruining things?
- Why... - I met my mother last week.
(Scratching)
- She's about to get married. - What's wrong with you?
She said my father kept his strong personality...
(Firm)
hidden for three years.
Did his character suddenly pop out after three years?
(Jong Kook's father revealed his true personality after 3 years.)
- Like that? - Suddenly.
- It wouldn't have been easy. - She must have been shocked.
It's moving when someone is nice to you when you're sick.
(Back to the talk about the groom-to-be)
- That's right. It's moving. - It feels different.
- He's also good at studying. - He's also good at studying.
- He reads a lot of books. - He even studies well?
- He went to Hongik University. - He's a Hongik University...
(Feeling proud)
- engineering graduate. - Hongik University engineering.
- He's an engineering graduate? - He's an engineering graduate.
(The dancer groom-to-be's surprising major)
- Because... - You know...
She cares about people's educational background.
- He always reads. - He reads all the time.
(He knows Vata well.)
- Really? - Really?
(He's quite different from the groom-to-be.)
We're not compatible in terms of knowledge.
- So... - How nice.
does Vata's family like you?
So much.
- They love me so much. - So much.
(The bride-to-be Ddochi is loved by her in-laws.)
Your father-in-law...
- cherishes you. - They love you so much?
She's starting her real life now.
(The life of a married person)
- Now, she's entering... - Nice.
They're so nice. They watch Running Man every week.
(The future parents-in-law)
I couldn't go to Jong Kook's concert because I had to go to Chungju.
- Right. - To meet my mother-in-law.
- Mother-in-law? - To meet my mother-in-law.
- She lives in Chungju? - Chungju.
(The in-laws)
- Chungju! - Chungju Ji!
- Chungju Ji and Jee cross! - Ji and Jee!
- Really? - She lives in Chungju.
How is it that Vata is from Chungju?
(A miraculous connection of Chungju with her in-laws)
- I know, right? - That's so interesting.
His parents live in Chungju.
- They farm there. - That's so interesting.
- Really? - They grow chili peppers as well.
- It was destiny. - "Milkshake" was your destiny.
It was destiny. "Milkshake" was...
(Ye Eun's marriage was expected from the "Milkshake" days.)
- It's Chungju Ji and Jee. - That's also so...
- It's a connection. - That's fascinating.
- Right. - The making of "Milkshake..."
(Feeling proud)
- played a big part. - It really did.
Did Vata propose to you?
He did.
How...
(Her voice gets all cutesy at the mention of a proposal.)
Tell us. How did he propose to you?
I feel shy telling such stories.
- Tell us. - What's wrong with that?
One day...
(Laughing)
- My gosh. - "One day..."
(Speaking in a raspy voice)
Vata...
- Vata! - "One day..."
You're the one who's telling the story.
(A hilariously goofy bride-to-be, gushing nonstop)
- Vata! - Gosh, Ji Ye Eun...
- It was... - It's so captivating.
a really tough day for me.
I had way too many shooting schedules.
- It was an exhausting day. - I was tired and exhausted.
(Too immersed)
I told him I'd be home late.
(I think I'll be late today.)
But he kept asking me where I was.
(Where are you about?)
I said it seemed like I still had...
(I have a few more hours to go.)
- a few more hours to go. - He prepared something.
Then...
I opened the door and walked in.
- And... - Candles?
(He just finds it hilarious.)
- Balloons? - And...
There were balloons...
- and a path made with candles. - Okay.
I thought...
he hired some event planner or something.
- I thought he hired someone. - Why are you about to cry?
- No. - She's moved to tears.
(Thinking about that moment overwhelms her.)
- She's choking up again. - So,
- he read me a letter he wrote. - Okay.
And he gave me a ring.
(Just a ring)
- A ring? - What?
A ring?
You know the thing women always want.
Tiffany.
- Tiffany? - Hey.
(Overdose on happiness)
- Mint. - Gosh, Ji Ye Eun.
Actually, I'm not so into that kind of stuff.
(Mumbling)
I have no interest...
- in rings or things like that. - You're not interested.
- But you know the design. - As soon as I saw the mint color...
(A mint ring box that made Ddochi thrilled)
- "My goodness!" - "This is a first for me."
- The mint... - Was it your first Tiffany?
- It was a first for me. - First?
So that was your first time ever receiving something like that.
(She's cute.)
That's how I got proposed to that day.
- After a warm hug, you cried. - After a hug,
I cried.
- And we cleaned up the balloons. - You cleaned them up.
That was nice.
(A proposal story, half gushy and half raspy)
- Great. - That's really romantic.
You got rid of the balloons so fast.
- You cleaned them up together? - That was really fast.
(Truly happy)
- I have a question. - Okay.
So, where are you guys going for your honeymoon?
- Have you decided on a place? - Have you?
I'd love to get some recommendations.
- Southern France. - Southern France?
- It's really nice. - How much time can you take off?
- Will you clear my schedule? - Sure.
(To the director)
- A week? - We can just go with you.
- A week is too short. - That would be nice.
- Stop joking around. - I'd like to go with you.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
(Taking the idea right away)
- We're really going. - We are really going with you.
(Hyenas pouncing at the first chance)
- Can we really do that? - We're coming with you.
- Ye Eun, we're coming. - We're serious.
- Then you can take two weeks off. - Really?
- If you let us tag along. - Of course.
- We can shoot there. - If you let us come.
Then you should come. Really.
You guys can just come with us,
hang out with us for a bit, and then leave.
- I did the same thing. - At Gimpo Airport...
(During the "Infinite Challenge" period)
I mean, we can part ways at Incheon International Airport.
- We can shoot 2 episodes there. - Right, 2 episodes.
- Then we will let you go. - After shooting two episodes?
(The honeymoon race is taking shape.)
- I'm totally in. - That sounds great.
So we will be shooting for about two days.
But I'm pretty sure that by the second day,
Ye Eun will be crying by herself.
"Why are you crying? What's wrong?"
(She's going to cry due to the shattered honeymoon fantasies.)
- "Please stop it." - "It's nothing."
- And she will be blushing. - "I'm the bride here."
This is really nice.
- It really is. - Congratulations.
- Congratulations. - Anyway, her wedding is...
- in December. - Right.
(Congratulations on becoming a December bride.)
I hope you prepare well for the wedding until then.
We wish you a beautiful life together.
(Bride-to-be Ye Eun is going to work even harder.)
- Congratulations! - Congratulations!
- Congratulations. - I'm so happy for you.
- When the wedding gets closer... - All right.
Shall we get going now?
(Cut!)
- Take the cake with you. - Oh, the cake.
(Episodes on September 20 and September 27...)
- Let's eat it together. - Let's eat.
(won't air due to the Asian sports event.)
- Let's share it. - Go ahead and eat.
- Let's eat it after lunch. - Let's do that.
- After lunch. - Let's eat it after the meal.
All right. Pack it away.
(Running Man)